{
    "id": "Covid-19_126",
    "claim": "The report “Reported Consent Disclosure to Vaccine Trial Subjects of Risk of COVID-19 Vaccine Wortering Clinical Disease“, published in the International Journal of Clinical Practice on 28 October 2020, states that “COVID-19 vaccines designed to induce neutralising antibodies can sensitize vaccine recipients to a more serious disease than if they were not vaccinated”. According to the study:“Vaccinations against SARS, MRS and RSV have never been authorised and data obtained during the development and testing of these vaccines indicate a serious concern: That vaccines developed empirically using the traditional approach (consisting of unmodified or minimally modified coronavirus spike that produces neutralising antibodies), whether they are made of protein, viral vector, DNA or RNA, and regardless of the method of administration, may aggravate COVID-19 disease by means of antibody-dependent amplification (ADE). This risk is disguised in clinical trial protocols and in the informed consent forms of ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials, to the extent that patients are unlikely to understand this risk adequately, so that a truly informed consent of the subjects of these trials is not possible. The specific and significant risk of ADE COVID-19 should have been prominently and independently disclosed to vaccine trial participants, as well as those being recruited for trials and future patients after vaccine approval, in order to comply with the medical ethical standard of patient understanding for informed consent. “What is antibody-dependent amplification? As the authors of this news report pointed out in the International Journal of Clinical Practice, previous efforts to vaccinate against the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS-CoV), the Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS-CoV) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) – have raised serious concerns. These vaccines have a tendency to trigger antibody-dependent amplification. What exactly does that mean?In short, it means that the vaccine does not strengthen your immunity to infection, but the ability of the virus to enter and infect your cells, resulting in a more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated. This is exactly the opposite of what a vaccine is supposed to do and a significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine 19. The 2003 summary document entitled “Antibody-Dependent Enhancement of Virus Infection and Disease” explains:“In general, virus-specific antibodies are considered antiviral and play an important role in the control of viral infections in various ways. However, in some cases, the presence of specific antibodies against the virus may be beneficial. This activity is known as antibody-dependent amplification (ADE) of virus infection. The DDA of viral infection is a phenomenon in which the specific antibodies of the virus interact with the Fc and/or complement receptors to promote the entry of the virus into the monocytes/macrophages and granulocyte cells and, in some cases, the replication of the virus. This phenomenon has been reported in vitro and in vivo in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health. These viruses share some common characteristics, such as preferential replication in macrophages, the ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity. For some viruses, the infection ADE has become a major problem in the control of the disease through vaccination. “Previous efforts of the coronavirus vaccine have failed in my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020, he summarized the history of the development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS. Until 2012, Chinese, American and European scientists were working on the development of SARS vaccines and had about 30 promising candidates. Of these, the four best candidates for the vaccine were given to ferrets, which present lung infections closest to human infections. In the interview, Kennedy explains what happened next. Although ferrets showed a robust antibody response, which is the measure for vaccine approval, as soon as they faced the wild virus, they all became seriously ill and died. The same happened when they tried to develop an RSV vaccine in the 1960s. RSV is a disease of the upper respiratory tract very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses. At that time, they decided to skip experiments on animals and move directly on to experiments on humans. Kennedy sagte: “They proved it, I think, in 35 children, and the same thing happened. Children developed a strong, long-lasting, champone antibody response. It looked perfect, but when the children were exposed to the wild virus, they all got sick. Two of them died. They left the vaccine. It was a great shame for the FDA [Food and Drug Administration] and the NIH [National Institutes of Health]. “Crone viruses not only cause the production of one type, but two different types of antibodies: Neutralizing antibodies, also known as immunoglobulin G (IgG) antibodies, which combat infection Agglutating antibodies, also known as non-neutralizing antibodies, which cannot prevent viral infectionInstead of preventing viral infection, binding antibodies trigger an abnormal immune response, called “paradoxic immune increase”. Another way to look at it is that your immune system doesn't work to protect you, but it makes you sicker. Many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market use mRNA to instruct your cells to produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein (S protein). The tip protein, which adheres to the cell's ACE2 receptor, is the first stage of the two-step process that viruses use to enter cells. The idea is that by forming SARS-CoV-2 tip protein, your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick. The key question is, which of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?Without neutralizing antibodies, more serious diseases are expectedThe Immunologist wrote on his Twitter channel in April 2020:“In the development of vaccines..and considering immunity passports, we must first understand the complex role of antibodies in SARS, MRS and COVID-19. “It lists other coronavirus vaccine studies that have raised concerns about ADE. The first is a 2017 study on the pathogen PLOS, Enhanced Inflammation in New Zealand White Rabbits When MERS-CoV Reinfection Occurs in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody, which investigated whether infection with MERS would protect tested animals from re-infection, as is usually the case with many viral diseases. (This means that once you have recovered from a viral infection, such as measles, you are immune and no longer get sick again). To determine how MERS affects the immune system, researchers infected white rabbits with the virus. Rabbits became sick and developed antibodies, but these antibodies were not neutralizing, i.e. the type of antibodies that block the infection. As a result, they were not protected from re-infection, and when they were exposed to the MERS for the second time, they became ill again, and even more seriously. “In fact, the re-infection caused an increase in pneumonia without increasing the concentration of viral RNA,” the authors said. Interestingly, this second infection produced neutralising antibodies that prevented animals from becoming infected for the third time. The authors explained:“Our rabbit model data suggest that individuals who have been exposed to MERS-CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response, or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased, may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re-exposing to MERS-CoV. “In other words: If the vaccine does not produce a robust response to neutralising antibodies, infection with the virus may put the patient at risk of developing a more serious lung disease. And here's an important point: COVID-19 vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection. As described in the News “How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged“, a “successful” vaccine only needs to reduce the severity of symptoms. It's not even about reducing infection, hospitalization, or death rates. ADE in dengue infections Dengue virus is also known to cause ADE. As explained in a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020:“(..) the pathogenesis of COVID-19 is currently supposed to occur through direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms. An additional mechanism that facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage may be called antibody-dependent amplification (ADE). ADE is a known cascade of events in which viruses can infect susceptible cells by interaction between virions complexed with antibodies or complement components and Fc or complement receptors, leading to increased replication. This phenomenon is of enormous importance not only for the understanding of viral pathogenesis, but also for the development of antiviral strategies, in particular vaccines. (..)There are four dengue virus serotypes, all of which produce protective immunity. Although homotypic protection is durable, cross neutralising antibodies against different serotypes are short-lived and can only last up to 2 years. In dengue fever, re-infection with another serotype is more severe when the concentration of protective antibodies decreases. Here, non-neutralizing antibodies overlap neutralizers, bind to dengue virus virions, and these complexes mediate phagocyte cell infection through interaction with the Fc receptor, in a typical ADE. In other words, heterotypic antibodies at subneutralizing concentrations are responsible for ADE in individuals infected with a dengue virus serotype different from the initial infection. Cross-reaction neutralising antibodies are associated with a lower probability of symptomatic secondary infection and the higher the concentration of those antibodies after primary infection, the greater the delay in symptomatic secondary infection (..). “The document further examines the detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow-up studies, which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non-vaccinated control group. The explanation for this seems to be that the vaccine imitated a primary infection, and as this immunity weakened, the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time. The author explains:“A post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test to distinguish antibodies caused by a wild-type infection that occurred after vaccination showed that the vaccine could protect against severe dengue [in] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination and that the risk of a serious clinical outcome increased in seronegative individuals. On this basis, a strategic expert group convened by the World Health Organization (WHO) concluded that only dengue-positive individuals should be vaccinated if dengue control programmes including vaccination are planned. “ADE in Coronavirus InfectionsThis may ultimately be relevant for the COVID-19 vaccine. Hypothetically speaking: If SARS-CoV-2 acts like dengue, which is also caused by an RNA virus, then anyone who is not positive in the SARS-CoV-2 test could actually have an increased risk of severe COVID-19 after vaccination, and only those who have already recovered from a COVID-19 attack would be protected from severe disease by the vaccine. Let's be clear:We don't know if this is the case or not, but these are important areas of research and the ongoing vaccine studies simply won't be able to answer this important question. The Swiss Medical Weekly document also examines ADE tests on coronavirus infections and cites research that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV (feline infectious peritonitis virus) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine. “Experiments have shown that immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induced lung immunopathology when exposed to SARS virus. “The paper also cites research showing that “the antibodies induced by a vaccine against SARS-CoV amplify infection of B cell lines despite the protective reactions of the hamster model”. In another document, published in 2014, it was found that antibody-dependent SARS coronavirus infection is mediated by antibodies against puncture proteins:“(..) the highest levels of antisera against SARS-CoV neutralized SARS-CoV infection, while highly diluted antisera significantly increased SARS-CoV infection and induced higher levels of apoptosis. Infectiousity test results indicate that SARS-CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins. We also generated monoclonal antibodies against SARS-CoV tip proteins and observed that most of them promoted SARS-CoV infection. Overall, our results suggest that antibodies to SARS-CoV tip proteins can trigger the effects of ADE. The data raises new questions about a possible vaccine against SARS-CoV (..). “A study following this was published in the JCI Insight magazine in 2019. Here, macaques vaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus (MVA), which encodes SARS-CoV tip protein of full length, ended up with a more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus. And when they transferred IgG anti-spike antibodies to unvaccinated macaques, they developed acute diffuse alveolar damage, probably because of “distorting the resolution response of inflammation”. The SARS vaccine aggravates infection after infection with SARS-CoVAn interesting 2012 news story with the revealing title “Immunization with SARS Coronavirus Vaccines Leads to Pulmonary Immunopathology on Challenge with the SARS Virus” shows what many researchers now fear, namely that COVID-19 vaccines can make people more susceptible to serious SARS-CoV-2 infections. The paper provides an overview of experiments that show that immunization with various vaccines against SARS resulted in lung immunopathology that eventually faced SARS virus. As the authors pointed out:“Inactivated vaccines against the whole virus, whether inactivated with formalin or beta-propylactone and administered with or without alum adjuvant, showed an immunopathological type Th2 in the lungs after the challenge. As mentioned above, immunopathology was attributed in two reports to the presence of protein N in the vaccine; however, the same immunopathological response was found in animals to which only the S-protein vaccine was administered, although it appeared to be less intense. Thus, an immunopathological response of type Th2 to the infection of vaccinated animals occurred in three of the four animal models (not in hamsters), including two different strains of mice endogamous with four different types of vaccines against SARS-CoV with and without alum adjuvant. No inactivated vaccine preparation has been reported to induce this result in non-human mice, ferrets and primates. Taken together, these experiences give rise to concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS-CoV in humans. Clinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines have been conducted which have been reported to induce antibody responses and are ‘safe'. However, the safety test has only been provided for a short observation period. The concern raised in this report concerns the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS-CoV infectious virus, which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine. Other safety concerns relate to the efficacy and safety against antigenic variants of the severe acute respiratory syndrome virus (SARS-CoV) and the safety of people exposed to other krone viruses, in particular those in the type 2 group. “Older people are the most vulnerable to ADEIn addition to all these concerns, there is evidence that older people, who are the most affected by severe COVID-19 diseases, are also the most affected by ADE. A preliminary investigation published on the medRxiv prepress server at the end of March 2020 reported that middle-aged and elderly patients with COVID-19 have much higher concentrations of anti-spike antibodies – which in turn increase infectivity – than younger patients. Strengthening Immunity Is a Serious ConcernAnother document worth mentioning is the mini-review of May 2020 “Impact of immune enhancement on Covid-19 polyclonal hyperimmune globulin therapy and vaccine development” (Effects of immune enhancement in polyclonal hyperimmunoglobulin therapy COVID-19 and vaccine development). As in many other studies, the authors point out that:“While the development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine is promising, both present a common theoretical safety problem. Experimental studies have suggested that SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections may increase immunity, which may occur similarly in SARS-CoV-2 infection (..). Theoretically, there are two ways to strengthen the immune increase of the disease. First, non-neutralizing or sub-neutralizing amounts of antibodies can amplify SARS-CoV-2 infection in target cells. Second, antibodies could increase inflammation and therefore the severity of lung disease. Figure 1 summarizes an overview of these antibody-dependent infectious and immunopathological augmentation effects (..). Several candidates for SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV vaccine are currently in initial preclinical or clinical trials. Animal studies on these CoVs have shown that vaccines based on protein S (especially receptor binding domain, RBD) are highly immunogenic and protect against the challenge of wild type CoVs. Vaccines that target other parts of the virus, such as nucleocapside, without S protein, have not shown protection against CoV infection and increased lung pathology. However, immunization with some protein S-based CoV vaccines has also shown signs of increased lung pathology following infection with the virus. Therefore, in addition to the choice of antigen target, the efficacy of the vaccine and the risk of immunopathology may depend on other additional factors, such as the formulation of the adjuvant, the age of vaccination (..) and the route of immunization. “• BILD EINFÜGEN • NACHFOLGEND UNTERSTRICHEN MARKIERTE BILDBESCHREIBUNG • Antibody-mediated ADE and immunopathology • Left Panel: In ADE, the internalization of the immune complex is mediated by the involvement of activated Fc receptors on the cell surface. Collegation of inhibitor receptors then leads to inhibition of antiviral reactions, leading to increased viral replication. Right Panel: Antibodies may cause immunopathology by activating the complement pathway or antibody-dependent cell cytotoxicity (ADCC). In both ways, excessive immunological activation leads to the release of cytokines and chemokines, resulting in an increase in disease pathology. The important risk-benefit analysis before decidingIn all probability, regardless of how effective (or ineffective) COVID-19 vaccines are, they will reach the public in a relatively short time. Most predict that one or more vaccines will be ready sometime in 2021. Ironically, the data we have now no longer support a mass vaccination mandate, considering that the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza. If you're under 40, your risk of dying from COVID-19 is only 0.01%, which means you have a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection. And you could improve it to 99.999% if you're metabolically flexible and rich in vitamin D. So, what are we protecting ourselves from with a vaccine against COVID-19?As already mentioned, vaccines are not even designed to prevent infection, but only to reduce the severity of symptoms. In the meantime, you might get sick more once you're exposed to the virus. This seems to be a great risk to a truly questionable benefit. To get back to the starting point: Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials are not informed of this risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus. Fatal immunopathology Th2 is another potential risk.Finally, think about what the information from the PNAS says about the risk of increase and dysfunction of the immune system induced by the vaccine, especially for the elderly, the same people who would need the protection that a vaccine should provide:\"Since the 1960s, tests of candidate vaccines for diseases such as dengue, syncitial respiratory virus (SRI) and severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) have shown a paradoxical phenomenon:Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus developed a more serious disease than those who had not been vaccinated. The immune system supported by the vaccine seemed to trigger an incorrect response to natural infection in certain cases (..). This reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement, can manifest itself in several ways, including antibody-dependent enhancement (ADE), a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection, or cell-based enhancement, a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology. In some cases, improvement processes can overlap (..). Some researchers argue that although ADE has received the greatest attention so far, according to what is known about the epidemiology of the virus and its behavior in the human body, it is less likely to occur than a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement. ‘ADE may occur, but the biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology', says Ralph Baric, an epidemiologist and coronavirus expert (..) at North Carolina University in Chapel Hill. In previous studies on SARS, it was discovered that older mice were at a particularly high risk of developing a life-threatening Th2 immunopathology, (..) in which a defective T-cell response triggers allergic inflammation and malfunctioning antibodies that form immune complexes activate the complement system and can damage the respiratory tract. “",
    "source": "2020news.de",
    "date": "25/11/2020",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "The report “Reported Consent Disclosure to Vaccine Trial Subjects of Risk of COVID-19 Vaccine Wortering Clinical Disease get The report “Reported Consent Disclosure to Vaccine Trial Subjects of Risk of COVID-19 Vaccine Wortering Clinical Disease 35 children unvaccinated macaques the virus unvaccinated macaques get hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine a strong, long-lasting, champone antibody response expectedThe Immunologist Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials SARS virus MERS-CoV SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections the vaccine can sensitize vaccine recipients to a more Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials SARS-CoV-2 than SARS the virus not vaccinateda tendency to trigger antibody-dependent amplification .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many children got hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine?",
                    "answer": "35 children unvaccinated macaques"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the virus that can sensitize vaccine recipients to a stronger antibody response?",
                    "answer": "SARS virus MERS-CoV SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID-19 Vaccine Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8041,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoV-2|compound\tthe ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|pobj\tthe ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the COVID-19 Vaccine Wortering Clinical Disease Vaccine and MERS-CoV-2 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8035,
                    "answers": "expectedThe|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of the COVID-CoV-2 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.802,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoV-2 vaccine a strong , long - lasting , champone antibody response|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Consent Disclosure to Vaccine Subjects of Risk of COVID-19 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8013,
                    "answers": "SARS the virus|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7978,
                    "answers": "COVID-19|nmod\tCOVID-19|nmod\tCOVID-19|compound\tCOVID-19|nummod\tto trigger antibody - dependent amplification|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "a tendency to trigger antibody-dependent amplification study:“Vaccinations against SARS, MRS and RSV SARS-CoVAn MERS-CoV been authorised and the coronavirus vaccine the pathogen The SARS vaccine my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020 SARS-CoV-2 SARS virus my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020 vaccinated people the vaccine vaccinated people MERS-CoV vaccines developed empirically using the traditional approach (consisting of unmodified or minimally modified coronavirus spike that produces neutralising antibodies) the coronavirus vaccine SARS virus vaccines developed empirically using the traditional approach (consisting of unmodified or minimally modified coronavirus spike that produces neutralising antibodies) SARS vaccines developed empirically using the traditional approach (consisting of unmodified or minimally modified coronavirus spike that produces neutralising antibodies) COVID-19 SARS the vaccine vaccines developed empirically using the traditional approach (consisting of unmodified or minimally modified coronavirus spike that produces neutralising antibodies) Chinese, American and European scientists SARS virus the vaccine Chinese, American and European scientists SARS-CoVAn are COVID-19 protein, viral vectorCOVID-19 vaccines MERS-CoV SARS-CoVAn about 30 promising candidates administration, may aggravate Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the pathogen?",
                    "answer": "the coronavirus vaccine"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the pathogen?",
                    "answer": "coronavirus vaccine"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What vaccines were developed empirically using the traditional approach?",
                    "answer": "SARS vaccines"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What vaccine was developed empirically using the traditional approach?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19 SARS"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people were vaccinated against the SARS virus?",
                    "answer": "about 30 promising candidates administration, may aggravate Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How are coronavirus vaccines developed empirically using traditional approaches?",
                    "score": 0.8688,
                    "answers": "MERS - CoV|compound\tMERS - CoV|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What method did Robert Kennedy use to develop the coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8515,
                    "answers": "empirically|advmod\ttraditional|amod\tempirically|advmod\ttraditional|amod\tempirically|advmod\ttraditional|amod\tempirically|advmod\ttraditional|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who created the coronavirus vaccine SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.8316,
                    "answers": "Chinese , American and European scientists|appos\tChinese , American and European scientists|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people received the coronavirus vaccine in May 2020?",
                    "score": 0.8266,
                    "answers": "Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus|ROOT\twho received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Robert Kennedy say about the coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8225,
                    "answers": "may|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus ADEIn SARS virus trial my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020 We Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020 the pathogen Rabbits forms of ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials SARS-CoV tip proteins ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials the vaccine COVID-19 patients Cross-reaction neutralising antibodies The tip protein, which adheres to the cell's ACE2 receptor the virus COVID-19 the same immunopathological response This reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did I interview in May 2020?",
                    "answer": "Robert Kennedy Jr."
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the tip protein adhere to?",
                    "answer": "the cell's ACE2 receptor"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Robert Kennedy Jr. say about the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.731,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\t25/11/2020|pobj\tthat|mark\tSome|det\tor|cc\twho|nsubj\twho received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus|relcl\tthe|det\tand|cc\tlater|advmod\tlater exposed themselves to the virus|conj\tthemselves|dobj\tthe|det\tthe virus|pobj\tthat Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus ADEIn SARS virus trial my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020|dobj\tmy|poss\tRobert|compound\tKennedy|compound\t2020|nummod\tWe Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020|punct\tRobert|compound\tKennedy|compound\t2020|nummod\tthe|det\tongoing|amod\t-|punct\ttip|compound\tongoing|amod\tthe|det\tCross|amod\t-|amod\treaction|npadvmod\tThe|det\ttip|compound\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe|det\tThis|det\tof the immune system|prep\tthe|det\timmune|amod\tthe immune system|pobj\t,|punct\timmune|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people received the COVID-19 vaccine in May 2020?",
                    "score": 0.7099,
                    "answers": "people|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7043,
                    "answers": "SARS virus|compound\tSARS - CoV|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7025,
                    "answers": "of ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6969,
                    "answers": "Cross - reaction neutralising antibodies The tip protein , which adheres to the cell 's ACE2 receptor the virus COVID-19 the same immunopathological response This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection This reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection Rabbits COVID-19 been a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection and independently disclosed SARS virus vaccine was participantsvaccinated children under 9 years of age the virus FIPV (feline infectious peritonitis virus) – a feline coronavirus – COVID-19 FIPV (feline infectious peritonitis virus) – a feline coronavirus – Th2 with the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV (feline infectious peritonitis virus) – a feline coronavirus – SARS-CoVAn .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that this reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the odds of surviving the virus FIPV?",
                    "score": 0.7594,
                    "answers": "Rabbits|appos\tCOVID-19|appos\tindependently|advmod\tindependently disclosed|amod\twas|dep\tparticipantsvaccinated|amod\t9|nummod\tof age|prep\tCOVID-19|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is FIPV?",
                    "score": 0.7468,
                    "answers": "SARS virus|compound\tparticipantsvaccinated children under 9 years of age the virus FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – COVID-19 FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – Th2 with the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – SARS - CoVAn|npadvmod\tage|pobj\tthe virus FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – COVID-19 FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – Th2 with the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – SARS - CoVAn|appos\tFIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|appos\tfeline|amod\tinfectious|amod\tperitonitis|compound\tfeline infectious peritonitis virus|appos\tfeline|amod\ta feline coronavirus|appos\tCOVID-19 FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|appos\tfeline|amod\tinfectious|amod\tperitonitis|compound\tfeline infectious peritonitis virus|appos\tfeline|amod\ta feline coronavirus|appos\tTh2 with the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|appos\twith the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|prep\tmedical|amod\tethical|amod\tthe medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|pobj\tof patient understanding|prep\tpatient|compound\tpatient understanding|pobj\tfor FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|prep\tFIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus )|pobj\tfeline|amod\tinfectious|amod\tperitonitis|compound\tfeline infectious peritonitis virus|appos\tfeline|amod\ta feline coronavirus – SARS - CoVAn|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoVAn?",
                    "score": 0.7466,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoVAn|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is immune enhancement?",
                    "score": 0.734,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection Rabbits COVID-19 been a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection and independently disclosed SARS virus vaccine was participantsvaccinated children under 9 years of age the virus FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – COVID-19 FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – Th2 with the medical ethical imitated of patient understanding for FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – SARS - CoVAn|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\t25/11/2020|pobj\tthat|mark\tThis|det\tThis reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection Rabbits COVID-19|nsubj\tof the immune system|prep\tthe|det\timmune|amod\tthe immune system|pobj\t,|punct\tknown as immune enhancement|acl\tas immune enhancement|prep\timmune|amod\timmune enhancement|pobj\ta|det\t99.99|nummod\t99.99 %|compound\ta 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|appos\tof surviving the infection|prep\tsurviving the infection|pcomp\tthe|det\tthe infection|dobj\tThis|det\tThis reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|appos\tof the immune system|prep\tthe|det\timmune|amod\tthe immune system|pobj\t,|punct\tknown as immune enhancement|acl\tas immune enhancement|prep\timmune|amod\timmune enhancement|pobj\ta|det\t99.99|nummod\t99.99 %|compound\ta 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|appos\tof surviving the infection|prep\tsurviving the infection|pcomp\tthe|det\tthe infection|dobj\tthat This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection Rabbits COVID-19 been a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection and independently disclosed SARS virus vaccine was|ccomp\ta|det\t99.99|nummod\t99.99 %|compound\ta 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|attr\tof surviving the infection|prep\tsurviving the infection|pcomp\tthe|det\tthe infection|dobj\tand|cc\t9 years of age|pobj\tthe|det\t(|punct\t)|punct\t–|punct\ta|det\t–|punct\t(|punct\t)|punct\t–|punct\ta|det\t–|punct\tthe|det\t(|punct\t)|punct\t–|punct\ta|det\t–|punct\t-|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "COVID-19 vaccinated children under 9 years of age -dependent the vaccine ? As the vaccinated children under 9 years of age of this news report pointed out in the International Journal of Clinical Practice, COVID-19 efforts to vaccinate against the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS-CoV), the Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS-CoV) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) – have raised serious concerns.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did 2020news.de say COVID-19 vaccinated children under 9 years of age?",
                    "answer": "-dependent the vaccine"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why did 2020news.de say COVID-19 vaccinated children under 9 years of age?",
                    "answer": "-dependent the vaccine"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are COVID-19 vaccines for children under 9 years of age?",
                    "score": 0.8396,
                    "answers": "children under 9 years of age|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are COVID-19 vaccination rates for children under 9?",
                    "score": 0.832,
                    "answers": "the vaccinated children under 9 years of age of this news report|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19 vaccination?",
                    "score": 0.8202,
                    "answers": "that COVID-19 vaccinated children under 9 years of age|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7727,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that COVID-19 vaccinated children under 9 years of age -dependent the vaccine ?|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tCOVID-19|nsubj\t9|nummod\t9 years of age|pobj\tof age|prep\tage|pobj\t-dependent|punct\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|dobj\t?|punct\tAs|mark\tthe|det\t9|nummod\t9 years of age|pobj\tof age|prep\tage|pobj\tof this news report|prep\tthis|det\tnews|compound\tthis news report|pobj\tAs the vaccinated children under 9 years of age of this news report pointed out in the International Journal of Clinical Practice|advcl\tout|prt\tin the International Journal of Clinical Practice|prep\tthe|det\tInternational|compound\tof Clinical Practice|prep\tClinical|compound\tClinical Practice|pobj\t,|punct\tCOVID-19|nmod\tCOVID-19 efforts to vaccinate against the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV ) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus ( RSV ) –|nsubj\tto|aux\tto vaccinate against the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV ) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus ( RSV ) –|acl\tagainst the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV ) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus ( RSV ) –|prep\tthe|det\tthe coronavirus|pobj\t–|punct\tagainst the severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV )|prep\tthe|det\tsevere|amod\tacute|amod\trespiratory|amod\tthe severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV )|pobj\t(|punct\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|appos\t)|punct\t,|punct\tthe|det\tMiddle|nmod\trespiratory|amod\trespiratory syndrome|nmod\t(|punct\tMERS|compound\t-|punct\t)|punct\tcoronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus ( RSV )|pobj\tand|cc\trespiratory|amod\tsyncytial|amod\trespiratory syncytial virus ( RSV )|conj\t(|punct\tRSV|appos\t)|punct\t–|punct\thave|aux\tAs the vaccinated children under 9 years of age of this news report pointed out in the International Journal of Clinical Practice , COVID-19 efforts to vaccinate against the coronavirus – against the severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS - CoV ) , the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV ) coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus ( RSV ) – have raised serious concerns|ROOT\tserious|amod\tserious concerns|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7598,
                    "answers": "the Middle East respiratory syndrome ( MERS - CoV )|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These vaccines have a tendency to trigger antibody-dependent amplification.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said vaccines have a tendency to trigger antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of vaccines on antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "score": 0.8502,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat These vaccines have a tendency to trigger antibody - dependent amplification|ccomp\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between vaccines and amplification?",
                    "score": 0.8042,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What exactly does that mean?In short, it means that the vaccine does not strengthen your immunity to infection, but the ability of the virus to enter and infect your cells, resulting in a more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said what on 25/11/2020?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the CDC say about vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8585,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that What exactly does that mean?In short|ROOT\tthat What exactly does that mean?In short|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the flu vaccination do to your immunity?",
                    "score": 0.8375,
                    "answers": "in a more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of vaccines on immunity?",
                    "score": 0.8094,
                    "answers": "that|mark\texactly|advmod\tdoes|aux\tthat|nsubj\tshort|amod\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tdoes|aux\tto infection|prep\tinfection|pobj\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe virus|pobj\tto|aux\tand|cc\t,|punct\tresulting in a more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated|conj\ta|det\tmore|advmod\tif|mark\tyou|nsubjpass\thad|aux\tbeen|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the mortality rate of the flu if you have not been vaccinated?",
                    "score": 0.7872,
                    "answers": "more serious|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the flu vaccination rate?",
                    "score": 0.775,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tWhat exactly|dobj\tnot|neg\tyour immunity to infection , but the ability of the virus to enter and infect your cells , resulting in a more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated|dobj\ta more serious disease than if you had not been vaccinated|pobj\tnot|neg"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This is exactly the opposite of what a vaccine is supposed to do and a significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine 19.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that this is exactly the opposite of what a vaccine is supposed to do?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7728,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This is exactly the opposite of a vaccine is supposed what to do and a significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine 19|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThis|nsubj\tthat This is exactly the opposite of a vaccine is supposed what to do and a significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|ccomp\texactly|advmod\tthe|det\texactly the opposite of a vaccine is supposed what to do and a significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|attr\tof a vaccine is supposed what to do|prep\twhat|dobj\ta|det\ta vaccine|nsubjpass\tis|auxpass\ta vaccine is supposed what to do|pcomp\tto|aux\twhat to do|xcomp\tand|cc\ta|det\tsignificant|amod\ta significant problem that was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|conj\tthat|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tthat was pointed out from the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|relcl\tout|prt\tfrom the beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tthe beginning of the demand for the COVID vaccine|pobj\tof the demand for the COVID vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tthe demand for the COVID vaccine|pobj\tfor the COVID vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tCOVID|compound\tthe COVID vaccine|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The 2003 summary document entitled “Antibody-Dependent Enhancement of Virus Infection and Disease” explains:“In general, virus-specific antibodies are considered antiviral and play an important role in the control of viral infections in various ways.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that The 2003 summary document entitled “Antibody-Dependent Enhancement of Virus Infection and Disease”?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What role does Antibody-Dependent Enhancement of Virus Infection and Disease play in control of viral infections?",
                    "score": 0.8401,
                    "answers": "an important role|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are virus-specific antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8093,
                    "answers": "virus - specific|amod\tvirus - specific antibodies|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the 2003 summary document say about viruses?",
                    "score": 0.7866,
                    "answers": "explains:“In general|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Antibody-Dependent Encephalic antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7415,
                    "answers": "various|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies and virus-specific antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7408,
                    "answers": "in various ways|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However, in some cases, the presence of specific antibodies against the virus may be beneficial.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What may be beneficial in some cases?",
                    "answer": "the presence of specific antibodies against the virus"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of the presence of specific antibodies against the virus?",
                    "score": 0.7651,
                    "answers": "in some cases|prep\tmay|aux\tbeneficial|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This activity is known as antibody-dependent amplification (ADE) of virus infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "answer": "antibody-dependent amplification"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "score": 0.7403,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This activity is known as antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE ) of virus infection|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat This activity is known as antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE ) of virus infection|ccomp\tas antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE ) of virus infection|prep\tantibody|npadvmod\t-|punct\tantibody - dependent|amod\t(|punct\tvirus|compound\tvirus infection|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "score": 0.726,
                    "answers": "antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE ) of virus infection|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "score": 0.7165,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|det\tThis activity|nsubjpass\tis|auxpass\t)|punct\tof virus infection|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6683,
                    "answers": "ADE )|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The DDA of viral infection is a phenomenon in which the specific antibodies of the virus interact with the Fc and/or complement receptors to promote the entry of the virus into the monocytes/macrophages and granulocyte cells and, in some cases, the replication of the virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the DDA of viral infection?",
                    "answer": "the specific antibodies of the virus interact with the Fc and/or complement receptors to promote the entry of the virus into the monocytes/macrophages and granulocyte cells"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What receptors do the specific antibodies of the virus interact with?",
                    "score": 0.7995,
                    "answers": "complement|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the DDA of viral infection consist of?",
                    "score": 0.7702,
                    "answers": "the specific antibodies of the virus|nsubj\twith the Fc and/or complement receptors|prep\tthe Fc and/or complement receptors|pobj\tcomplement receptors|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the replication of the virus?",
                    "score": 0.6946,
                    "answers": "the replication of the virus|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This phenomenon has been reported in vitro and in vivo in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How has this phenomenon been reported in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health?",
                    "answer": "in vitro and in vivo"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What has been reported in vitro and in vivo in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health?",
                    "score": 0.7519,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This phenomenon has been reported in vitro and in vivo in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health|ROOT\tthat|mark\tThis|det\tThis phenomenon|nsubjpass\thas|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tthat This phenomenon has been reported in vitro and in vivo in the case of viruses representing numerous families and genera of importance for public and veterinary health|ccomp\tvitro|pobj\tand|cc\tvivo|pobj\tthe|det\tand|cc\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is genera?",
                    "score": 0.6184,
                    "answers": "genera|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These viruses share some common characteristics, such as preferential replication in macrophages, the ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are some common characteristics of these viruses?",
                    "answer": "preferential replication in macrophages, the ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the common characteristics of these viruses?",
                    "score": 0.7628,
                    "answers": "These viruses|nsubj\tcommon|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the characteristics of preferential replication in macrophages?",
                    "score": 0.7396,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tThese|det\tsome|det\tsuch as preferential replication in macrophages , the ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity|prep\tpreferential|amod\tpreferential replication in macrophages , the ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity|pobj\tthe ability to establish persistence and antigenic diversity|conj\tto establish persistence and antigenic diversity|acl\tpersistence and antigenic diversity|dobj\tantigenic|amod\tantigenic diversity|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between preferential replication in macrophages and antigenic diversity?",
                    "score": 0.685,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t,|punct\tsuch|amod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tto|aux\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For some viruses, the infection ADE has become a major problem in the control of the disease through vaccination.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that for some viruses, the infection ADE became a major problem in the control of the disease?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many viruses have control of the disease through vaccination?",
                    "score": 0.7852,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that For some viruses , the infection ADE has become a major problem in the control of the disease through vaccination|ROOT\tthat For some viruses , the infection ADE has become a major problem in the control of the disease through vaccination|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between vaccination and ADE?",
                    "score": 0.691,
                    "answers": "through vaccination|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6778,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tFor some viruses|prep\tsome|det\tsome viruses|pobj\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe infection ADE|nsubj\tADE|appos\thas|aux\ta|det\tmajor|amod\tthe|det\tof the disease|prep\tthe|det\tthe disease|pobj\tvaccination|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“Previous efforts of the coronavirus vaccine have failed in my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020, he summarized the history of the development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the coronavirus vaccine begin?",
                    "answer": "2002"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Robert Kennedy Jr. say about coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7747,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ Previous efforts of the coronavirus vaccine have failed in my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr.|ccomp\tRobert|compound\tin May 2020|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the coronavirus vaccine in 2002?",
                    "score": 0.7418,
                    "answers": "of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|prep\tthe coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7163,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t“|punct\tPrevious|amod\tPrevious efforts of the coronavirus vaccine|nsubj\tof the coronavirus vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tthe coronavirus vaccine|pobj\thave|aux\tthat “ Previous efforts of the coronavirus vaccine have failed|ccomp\t2020|nummod\t,|punct\the|nsubj\t2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ Previous efforts of the coronavirus vaccine have failed in my interview with Robert Kennedy Jr. in May 2020 , he summarized the history of the development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|ROOT\tthe|det\tthe history of the development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|dobj\tof the development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|prep\tthe|det\tthe development of the coronavirus vaccine that began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|pobj\tthe|det\tthat|nsubj\tthat began in 2002 after three successive outbreaks of SARS|relcl\tin 2002|prep\tafter three successive outbreaks of SARS|prep\tsuccessive|amod\tthree successive outbreaks of SARS|pobj\tof SARS|prep\tSARS|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is coronavirus?",
                    "score": 0.6873,
                    "answers": "coronavirus|compound\tcoronavirus|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Until 2012, Chinese, American and European scientists were working on the development of SARS vaccines and had about 30 promising candidates.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many promising candidates did the Chinese, American and European scientists have for SARS vaccines?",
                    "answer": "30"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What countries were working on developing SARS vaccines until 2012?",
                    "score": 0.7889,
                    "answers": "Chinese , American and European|amod\tAmerican and European|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many promising candidates were there for SARS vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7881,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tpromising|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS?",
                    "score": 0.6261,
                    "answers": "on the development of SARS vaccines|prep\tthe development of SARS vaccines|pobj\tSARS|compound\tSARS vaccines|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Of these, the four best candidates for the vaccine were given to ferrets, which present lung infections closest to human infections.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of infections do ferrets have that are closest to human infections?",
                    "answer": "lung infections"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the four best candidates for the vaccine given to ferrets?",
                    "score": 0.7706,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\twhich present lung infections closest to human infections|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best cure for the flu?",
                    "score": 0.6515,
                    "answers": "best|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the interview, Kennedy explains what happened next.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that Kennedy explains what happened next?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Kennedy say about the interview?",
                    "score": 0.6746,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tthe interview|pobj\t,|punct\twhat|nsubj\twhat happened next|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Kennedy and Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6099,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Although ferrets showed a robust antibody response, which is the measure for vaccine approval, as soon as they faced the wild virus, they all became seriously ill and died.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that ferrets showed a robust antibody response?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many ferrets have a robust antibody response?",
                    "score": 0.7425,
                    "answers": "they|nsubj\tthey all|nsubj\tall|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many ferrets were seriously ill after the wild virus?",
                    "score": 0.7159,
                    "answers": "seriously ill|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process for vaccine approval?",
                    "score": 0.6682,
                    "answers": "wild|amod\tseriously|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many ferrets died from the wild virus in 2020?",
                    "score": 0.667,
                    "answers": "as they faced the wild virus|advcl\tdied|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the measure for vaccine approval?",
                    "score": 0.661,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Although ferrets showed a robust antibody response , which is the measure for vaccine approval , as soon as they faced the wild virus , they all became seriously ill and died|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAlthough|mark\tferrets|nsubj\tAlthough ferrets showed a robust antibody response , which is the measure for vaccine approval|advcl\ta|det\trobust|amod\tantibody|compound\ta robust antibody response , which is the measure for vaccine approval|dobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich is the measure for vaccine approval|relcl\tthe|det\tthe measure for vaccine approval|attr\tfor vaccine approval|prep\tvaccine|compound\tvaccine approval|pobj\t,|punct\tas|advmod\tas soon as they faced the wild virus|advmod\tas|mark\tthe|det\tthe wild virus|dobj\t,|punct\tthat Although ferrets showed a robust antibody response , which is the measure for vaccine approval , as soon as they faced the wild virus , they all became seriously ill and died|ccomp\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The same happened when they tried to develop an RSV vaccine in the 1960s.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the same happened when they tried to develop an RSV vaccine?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When was the RSV vaccine first developed?",
                    "score": 0.8954,
                    "answers": "in the 1960s|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the RSV vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7901,
                    "answers": "RSV|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "RSV is a disease of the upper respiratory tract very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is RSV caused by?",
                    "answer": "coronaviruses"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How similar is coronavirus to RSV?",
                    "score": 0.8123,
                    "answers": "very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between RSV and coronavirus?",
                    "score": 0.7206,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that RSV is a disease of the upper respiratory tract very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tRSV|nsubj\ta|det\ta disease of the upper respiratory tract very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses|attr\tof the upper respiratory tract|prep\tthe|det\tupper|amod\trespiratory|amod\tvery|advmod\tto the disease caused by coronaviruses|prep\tthe|det\tcoronaviruses|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is RSV?",
                    "score": 0.7136,
                    "answers": "that RSV is a disease of the upper respiratory tract very similar to the disease caused by coronaviruses|ccomp\tthe upper respiratory tract|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "At that time, they decided to skip experiments on animals and move directly on to experiments on humans.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that they decided to skip experiments on animals and move on to experiments on humans?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did scientists skip experiments on animals and move to experiments on humans?",
                    "score": 0.7796,
                    "answers": "animals|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the scientists decide to do with experiments on animals?",
                    "score": 0.6737,
                    "answers": "on animals|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What experiments were carried out on humans in 2020?",
                    "score": 0.6547,
                    "answers": "they|nsubj\tdirectly|advmod\tto experiments on humans|prep\texperiments on humans|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of experiments on animals in 2020?",
                    "score": 0.6097,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat|det\tthat time|pobj\t,|punct\tto|aux\texperiments on animals|dobj\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Kennedy sagte: “They proved it, I think, in 35 children, and the same thing happened.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What website said that Kennedy said that on 25/11/2020?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many children did Kennedy sagte teach?",
                    "score": 0.6841,
                    "answers": "They|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many children were born to Kennedy sagte?",
                    "score": 0.6561,
                    "answers": "that Kennedy sagte : “ They proved it , I think , in 35 children , and the same thing happened|ccomp\tthe same thing|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Kennedy sagte say about the claim?",
                    "score": 0.6312,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Kennedy sagte : “ They proved it , I think , in 35 children , and the same thing happened|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t:|punct\t“|punct\t“ They proved it , I think , in 35 children , and the same thing happened|ccomp\tit|dobj\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tI think|parataxis\t,|punct\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthe|det\tsame|amod\tthe same thing happened|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Children developed a strong, long-lasting, champone antibody response.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that Children developed a strong, long-lasting, champone antibody response?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the CDC say about champone antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8829,
                    "answers": "a strong , long - lasting , champone antibody response|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of antibodies did the children develop?",
                    "score": 0.8819,
                    "answers": "champone|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the study show about champone antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8804,
                    "answers": ",|punct\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to develop the champone antibody response?",
                    "score": 0.8463,
                    "answers": "that Children developed a strong , long - lasting , champone antibody response|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has it been since kids have developed a strong, long-lasting, champone antibody response?",
                    "score": 0.8189,
                    "answers": "long|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It looked perfect, but when the children were exposed to the wild virus, they all got sick.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the children got sick when they were exposed to the wild virus?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the statistics on children exposed to the wild virus?",
                    "score": 0.6934,
                    "answers": "perfect|acomp\tto the wild virus|prep\twild|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the wild virus?",
                    "score": 0.5777,
                    "answers": "the wild virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They left the vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that they left the vaccine on 25/11/2020?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between vaccines and the flu?",
                    "score": 0.7348,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat They left the vaccine|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7168,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThey|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of those who left the vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7122,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that They left the vaccine|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It was a great shame for the FDA [Food and Drug Administration] and the NIH [National Institutes of Health].",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that it was a great shame for the FDA and NIH?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the National Institute of Health stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6201,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat It was a great shame for the FDA [ Food and Drug Administration ] and the NIH [ National Institutes of Health ]|ccomp\tfor the FDA [ Food and Drug Administration ] and the NIH [ National Institutes of Health ]|prep\tthe FDA [ Food and Drug Administration ] and the NIH [ National Institutes of Health ]|pobj\tFood and Drug|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the shame for the FDA and the National Institutes of Health?",
                    "score": 0.6195,
                    "answers": "a great shame|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“Crone viruses not only cause the production of one type, but two different types of antibodies: Neutralizing antibodies, also known as immunoglobulin G (IgG) antibodies, which combat infection Agglutating antibodies, also known as non-neutralizing antibodies, which cannot prevent viral infectionInstead of preventing viral infection, binding antibodies trigger an abnormal immune response, called “paradoxic immune increase”.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happens to non-neutralizing antibodies instead of preventing viral infection?",
                    "answer": "binding antibodies trigger an abnormal immune response, called “paradoxic immune increase”"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of antibodies are Neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8688,
                    "answers": "25/11/2020|pobj\tthat|mark\t“|punct\tnot only|preconj\tonly|advmod\tthe|det\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tof antibodies|prep\tantibodies|pobj\t:|punct\tNeutralizing|amod\tNeutralizing antibodies , also known as immunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies , which combat infection Agglutating antibodies , also known as non - neutralizing antibodies , which can not prevent|dobj\t,|punct\talso|advmod\tas immunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies|prep\timmunoglobulin|nmod\timmunoglobulin G ( IgG )|nmod\t(|punct\t( IgG )|appos\t)|punct\timmunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies|pobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich combat infection|relcl\tinfection|dobj\t,|punct\talso|advmod\talso known as non - neutralizing antibodies|acl\tas non - neutralizing antibodies|prep\tnon|amod\t-|amod\tneutralizing|amod\tnon - neutralizing antibodies|pobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tcan|aux\tnot|neg\tviral|amod\tpreventing viral infection|pcomp\tviral|amod\tviral infection|dobj\t,|punct\tan|det\tabnormal|amod\timmune|amod\t,|punct\t“|punct\tparadoxic|amod\timmune|amod\t“ paradoxic immune increase|oprd\t”|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the properties of binding antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7521,
                    "answers": "binding|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of binding antibodies on immune response?",
                    "score": 0.7505,
                    "answers": "of preventing viral infection , binding antibodies trigger an abnormal immune response , called “ paradoxic immune increase ”|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many types of antibodies are there?",
                    "score": 0.7492,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ Crone viruses not only cause the production of one type , but two different types of antibodies : Neutralizing antibodies , also known as immunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies , which combat infection Agglutating antibodies , also known as non - neutralizing antibodies , which can not prevent viral infectionInstead of preventing viral infection , binding antibodies trigger an abnormal immune response , called “ paradoxic immune increase ”|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tCrone|compound\tCrone viruses not only|nsubj\tthat “ Crone viruses not only cause the production of one type , but two different types of antibodies : Neutralizing antibodies , also known as immunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies , which combat infection Agglutating antibodies , also known as non - neutralizing antibodies , which can not prevent|ccomp\tthe production of one type , but two different types of antibodies|dobj\tof one type , but two different types of antibodies|prep\tone type , but two different types of antibodies|pobj\tdifferent|amod\ttwo different types of antibodies|conj\tof preventing viral infection|prep\tan abnormal immune response , called “ paradoxic immune increase|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the two types of antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7462,
                    "answers": "also known as immunoglobulin G ( IgG ) antibodies|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Another way to look at it is that your immune system doesn't work to protect you, but it makes you sicker.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that Another way to look at it is that your immune system doesn't work to protect you?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How does the immune system work to protect you?",
                    "score": 0.7751,
                    "answers": "that Another way to look at it is that your immune system does n't work to protect you , but it makes you sicker|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What makes you sicker?",
                    "score": 0.6248,
                    "answers": "it makes you sicker|conj\tyou sicker|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to be sick?",
                    "score": 0.6216,
                    "answers": "Another way to look at it|nsubj\tto look at it|relcl\tthat your immune system does n't work to protect you , but it makes you sicker|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.5832,
                    "answers": "immune|amod\tyour immune system|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between immune system and immune system?",
                    "score": 0.5736,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Another way to look at it is that your immune system does n't work to protect you , but it makes you sicker|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAnother|det\tto|aux\tit|pobj\tthat|mark\tyour|poss\tdoes|aux\tn't|neg\tto|aux\tto protect you|advcl\tyou|dobj\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tit|nsubj\tyou|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market use mRNA to instruct your cells to produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein (S protein).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market use mRNA to instruct your cells to produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the COVID-19 vaccines use to produce SARS peak CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.8032,
                    "answers": "SARS peak CoV-2|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the COVID-19 vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7946,
                    "answers": "Many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market|nsubj\tthe COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many COVID-19 vaccines use mRNA?",
                    "score": 0.794,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market use mRNA to instruct your cells to produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein ( S protein )|ROOT\tcurrently on the market|relcl\tto|aux\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7721,
                    "answers": "of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of COVID-19 vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7543,
                    "answers": "that Many of the COVID-19 vaccines currently on the market use mRNA to instruct your cells to produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein ( S protein )|ccomp\tto produce SARS peak CoV-2 protein ( S protein )|xcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The tip protein, which adheres to the cell's ACE2 receptor, is the first stage of the two-step process that viruses use to enter cells.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that The tip protein is the first stage of the two-step process that viruses use to enter cells?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the first stage of the two step process that viruses use to enter cells?",
                    "score": 0.6977,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The tip protein , which adheres to the cell 's ACE2 receptor , is the first stage of the two - step process that viruses use to enter cells|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\ttip|compound\tThe tip protein , which adheres to the cell 's ACE2 receptor ,|nsubj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich adheres to the cell 's ACE2 receptor|relcl\tto the cell 's ACE2 receptor|prep\tthe|det\tthe cell 's|poss\t's|case\tACE2|compound\tthe cell 's ACE2 receptor|pobj\t,|punct\tthat The tip protein , which adheres to the cell 's ACE2 receptor , is the first stage of the two - step process that viruses use to enter cells|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe first stage of the two - step process that viruses use to enter cells|attr\tof the two - step process that viruses use to enter cells|prep\tthe|det\t-|punct\ttwo - step|compound\tthe two - step process that viruses use to enter cells|pobj\tthat|dobj\tviruses|nsubj\tthat viruses use to enter cells|relcl\tto|aux\tto enter cells|xcomp\tcells|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The idea is that by forming SARS-CoV-2 tip protein, your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that the idea is that by forming SARS-CoV-2 tip protein, your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2 tip protein?",
                    "score": 0.6836,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The idea is that by forming SARS - CoV-2 tip protein , your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tThe idea|nsubj\tthat The idea is that by forming SARS - CoV-2 tip protein , your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick|ccomp\tthat|mark\tby forming SARS - CoV-2 tip protein|prep\tforming SARS - CoV-2 tip protein|pcomp\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\ttip|compound\tSARS - CoV-2 tip protein|dobj\t,|punct\tyour|poss\timmune|amod\tyour immune system|nsubj\tthat by forming SARS - CoV-2 tip protein , your immune system starts producing antibodies without getting sick|ccomp\tproducing antibodies|xcomp\tantibodies|dobj\twithout getting sick|prep\tgetting sick|pcomp\tsick|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.6545,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoV-2|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The key question is, which of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?Without neutralizing antibodies, more serious diseases are expectedThe Immunologist wrote on his Twitter channel in April 2020:“In the development of vaccines..and considering immunity passports, we must first understand the complex role of antibodies in SARS, MRS and COVID-19.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that the key question is, which of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many types of antibodies are produced?",
                    "score": 0.6697,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The key question is , which of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?Without neutralizing antibodies|ROOT\tthat The key question is , which of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?Without neutralizing antibodies|ccomp\tof the two types of antibodies|prep\tthe two types of antibodies|pobj\twhich of the two types of antibodies is produced by this process?Without|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many serious diseases are expected without neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.6677,
                    "answers": ", more serious diseases are expectedThe|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the role of antibodies in the development of vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.6618,
                    "answers": "wrote on his Twitter channel in April 2020:“In the development of vaccines .. and considering immunity passports , we must first understand the complex role of antibodies in SARS , MRS and COVID-19|ROOT\tthe complex role of antibodies in SARS , MRS and COVID-19|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of the two types of antibodies produced?",
                    "score": 0.6444,
                    "answers": "which of the two types of antibodies|nsubjpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“It lists other coronavirus vaccine studies that have raised concerns about ADE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that it lists other coronavirus vaccine studies that raised concerns about ADE?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the other coronavirus vaccine studies?",
                    "score": 0.7838,
                    "answers": "other|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many coronavirus vaccine studies have raised concerns about ADE?",
                    "score": 0.7739,
                    "answers": "other coronavirus vaccine studies that have raised concerns about ADE|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of the coronavirus vaccine studies that raise concerns about ADE?",
                    "score": 0.7637,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ It lists other coronavirus vaccine studies that have raised concerns about ADE|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.757,
                    "answers": "coronavirus vaccine|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the coronavirus vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7406,
                    "answers": "that “ It lists other coronavirus vaccine studies that have raised concerns about ADE|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The first is a 2017 study on the pathogen PLOS, Enhanced Inflammation in New Zealand White Rabbits When MERS-CoV Reinfection Occurs in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody, which investigated whether infection with MERS would protect tested animals from re-infection, as is usually the case with many viral diseases.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the first study is a 2017 study on the pathogen PLOS, Enhanced Inflammation in New Zealand White Rabbits when MERS-CoV Reinfection Occurs in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV Reinfection?",
                    "score": 0.7512,
                    "answers": "Enhanced Inflammation in New Zealand White Rabbits When MERS - CoV Reinfection Occurs in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody|appos\tMERS - CoV Reinfection|nsubj\tWhen MERS - CoV Reinfection Occurs in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody|advcl\tof Neutralizing Antibody|prep\tthe case with many viral diseases|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the first study on the pathogen PLOS?",
                    "score": 0.7215,
                    "answers": "as is usually the case with many viral diseases|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7188,
                    "answers": "MERS|compound\tMERS - CoV|compound\tNeutralizing Antibody|pobj\tinfection with MERS|nsubj\tMERS|pobj\twhether infection with MERS would protect tested animals from re - infection , as is usually the case with many viral diseases|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV reception?",
                    "score": 0.6968,
                    "answers": "in the Absence of Neutralizing Antibody|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between MERS and MERS?",
                    "score": 0.6779,
                    "answers": "with MERS|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "(This means that once you have recovered from a viral infection, such as measles, you are immune and no longer get sick again).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that once you have recovered from a viral infection, you are immune and no longer get sick again?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to recover from a viral infection?",
                    "score": 0.7258,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThis|nsubj\tthat ( This means that once you have recovered from a viral infection , such as measles , you are immune and no longer get sick again )|ccomp\tthat|mark\tonce|mark\tyou|nsubj\thave|aux\ta|det\tviral|amod\t,|punct\tsuch|amod\t,|punct\tyou|nsubj\tthat once you have recovered from a viral infection , such as measles , you are immune and no longer get sick again|ccomp\tagain|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of a viral flu?",
                    "score": 0.6666,
                    "answers": "once you have recovered from a viral infection , such as measles|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a viral infection?",
                    "score": 0.6638,
                    "answers": "from a viral infection , such as measles|prep\ta viral infection , such as measles|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "To determine how MERS affects the immune system, researchers infected white rabbits with the virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was infected with MERS?",
                    "answer": "white rabbits"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How does MERS affect the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.871,
                    "answers": "how MERS affects the immune system|ccomp\tthe immune system|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of MERS on the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.694,
                    "answers": "To determine how MERS affects the immune system|advcl\tthat To determine how MERS affects the immune system , researchers infected white rabbits with the virus|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS?",
                    "score": 0.6936,
                    "answers": "MERS|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between MERS and the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.6574,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that To determine how MERS affects the immune system , researchers infected white rabbits with the virus|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tTo|aux\thow|advmod\tthe|det\t,|punct\tresearchers|nsubj\twhite|amod\twhite rabbits|dobj\twith the virus|prep\tthe|det\tthe virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Rabbits became sick and developed antibodies, but these antibodies were not neutralizing, i.e. the type of antibodies that block the infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said Rabbits became sick and developed antibodies?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of antibodies are used to block the HIV outbreak?",
                    "score": 0.8196,
                    "answers": "i.e.|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the types of antibodies that block the HIV infection?",
                    "score": 0.7688,
                    "answers": "that block the infection|relcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As a result, they were not protected from re-infection, and when they were exposed to the MERS for the second time, they became ill again, and even more seriously.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the patients were not protected from re-infection because they were exposed to MERS for a second time?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the MERS do to prevent re-infection?",
                    "score": 0.6952,
                    "answers": "that As a result , they were not protected from re - infection , and when they were exposed to the MERS for the second time , they became ill again , and even more seriously|ccomp\till|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened to the MERS after they were exposed to re-infection?",
                    "score": 0.6818,
                    "answers": "again|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people were exposed to the MERS for the second time?",
                    "score": 0.6245,
                    "answers": "As a result|prep\teven more|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the MERS?",
                    "score": 0.5598,
                    "answers": "the MERS|pobj\twhen they were exposed to the MERS for the second time , they became ill again , and even more seriously|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the MERS?",
                    "score": 0.5509,
                    "answers": "from re - infection|prep\tinfection|pobj\tand even more seriously|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“In fact, the re-infection caused an increase in pneumonia without increasing the concentration of viral RNA,” the authors said.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the authors of 2020news.de say about the re-infection?",
                    "answer": "the re-infection caused an increase in pneumonia without increasing the concentration of viral RNA,”"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the authors say about the re-infection?",
                    "score": 0.7091,
                    "answers": "the authors|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is viral RNA?",
                    "score": 0.7075,
                    "answers": "viral RNA|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the concentration of viral RNA?",
                    "score": 0.7028,
                    "answers": "without increasing the concentration of viral RNA|prep\tthe concentration of viral RNA|dobj\tof viral RNA|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between re-infection and viral RNA?",
                    "score": 0.6784,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ In fact , the re - infection caused an increase in pneumonia without increasing the concentration of viral RNA|ccomp\tthat|mark\t“|punct\tIn fact|prep\tfact|pobj\t,|punct\tthe|det\t-|nsubj\tan|det\tan increase in pneumonia|dobj\tin pneumonia|prep\tthe|det\t,|punct\t”|punct\tthe|det\t2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ In fact , the re - infection caused an increase in pneumonia without increasing the concentration of viral RNA , ” the authors said|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the amount of viral RNA?",
                    "score": 0.6719,
                    "answers": "viral|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Interestingly, this second infection produced neutralising antibodies that prevented animals from becoming infected for the third time.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the second infection produce that prevented animals from becoming infected for the third time?",
                    "answer": "neutralising antibodies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did the second infection produce neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8539,
                    "answers": "for the third time|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the effect of neutralizing antibodies on animals?",
                    "score": 0.772,
                    "answers": "neutralising antibodies that prevented animals from becoming infected for the third time|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many times has the second infection produced neutralizing antibodies that prevented animals from becoming infected?",
                    "score": 0.7591,
                    "answers": "the third time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many animals were infected by the second flu?",
                    "score": 0.7353,
                    "answers": "that prevented animals from becoming infected for the third time|relcl\tinfected|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the antibodies that prevent animals from becoming infected for the third time?",
                    "score": 0.676,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tInterestingly|advmod\t,|punct\tthis|det\tthat|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The authors explained:“Our rabbit model data suggest that individuals who have been exposed to MERS-CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response, or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased, may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re-exposing to MERS-CoV. “In other words: If the vaccine does not produce a robust response to neutralising antibodies, infection with the virus may put the patient at risk of developing a more serious lung disease.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the authors say about individuals who did not develop a neutralising antibody response or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased?",
                    "answer": "may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re-exposing to MERS-CoV."
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7654,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The authors explained:“Our rabbit model data suggest that individuals who have been exposed to MERS - CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response , or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased , may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\t25/11/2020|pobj\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tThe authors|nsubj\tthat The authors explained:“Our|punct\trabbit|compound\trabbit model|compound\trabbit model data|nsubj\trabbit model data suggest that individuals who have been exposed to MERS - CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response , or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased , may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|ccomp\tthat|mark\tindividuals who have been exposed to MERS - CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response , or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased ,|nsubj\twho|nsubjpass\thave|aux\tbeen|auxpass\twho have been exposed to MERS - CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response|relcl\tto MERS - CoV|prep\tMERS|compound\t-|punct\tMERS - CoV|pobj\tand|cc\tdo|aux\tnot|neg\tdo not develop a neutralising antibody response|conj\ta|det\tneutralising|amod\tantibody|compound\ta neutralising antibody response|dobj\t,|punct\tor|cc\tindividuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased ,|conj\twhose|poss\tneutralising|amod\tantibody|compound\twhose neutralising antibody concentrations|nsubj\thave|aux\twhose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased|relcl\t,|punct\tmay|aux\tthat individuals who have been exposed to MERS - CoV and do not develop a neutralising antibody response , or individuals whose neutralising antibody concentrations have decreased , may be at risk of developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|ccomp\tat risk of developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|prep\trisk of developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|pobj\tof developing severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|prep\tdeveloping severe lung disease by re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|pcomp\tsevere|amod\tlung|compound\tsevere lung disease|dobj\tby re - exposing to MERS - CoV.|prep\tre|pcomp\t-|pcomp\texposing to MERS - CoV.|pcomp\tto MERS - CoV.|prep\tMERS|compound\t-|punct\tMERS - CoV.|pobj\t“|punct\tIn other words|prep\tother|amod\tother words|pobj\t:|punct\tIf|mark\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|nsubj\tdoes|aux\tnot|neg\tIf the vaccine does not produce a robust response to neutralising antibodies|advcl\ta|det\trobust|amod\ta robust response to neutralising antibodies|dobj\tto neutralising antibodies|prep\tneutralising|amod\tneutralising antibodies|pobj\t,|punct\tinfection with the virus|nsubj\twith the virus|prep\tthe|det\tthe virus|pobj\tmay|aux\t“ In other words : If the vaccine does not produce a robust response to neutralising antibodies , infection with the virus may put the patient at risk of developing a more serious lung disease|ROOT\tthe|det\tthe patient|dobj\tat risk of developing a more serious lung disease|prep\trisk of developing a more serious lung disease|pobj\tof developing a more serious lung disease|prep\tdeveloping a more serious lung disease|pcomp\ta|det\tmore|advmod\tmore serious|amod\tlung|compound\ta more serious lung disease|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And here's an important point: COVID-19 vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that COVID-19 vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19 vaccines"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are COVID-19 vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8567,
                    "answers": "vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7581,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that And here 's an important point : COVID-19 vaccines are NOT meant to prevent infection|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\there|advmod\tthat And here 's an important point :|ccomp\tan|det\timportant|amod\tan important point|nsubj\t:|punct\tCOVID-19|punct\tvaccines|nsubjpass\tare|auxpass\tNOT|neg\tto|aux\tto prevent infection|xcomp\tinfection|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As described in the News “How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged“, a “successful” vaccine only needs to reduce the severity of symptoms.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did 2020news.de say about the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "answer": "a “successful” vaccine only needs to reduce the severity of symptoms"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How successful is COVID-19 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8568,
                    "answers": "successful|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7876,
                    "answers": "that As described in the News “ How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “ , a “ successful ” vaccine only needs to reduce the severity of symptoms|ccomp\tto reduce the severity of symptoms|xcomp\tthe severity of symptoms|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7855,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that As described in the News “ How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “ , a “ successful ” vaccine only needs to reduce the severity of symptoms|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAs|mark\tAs described in the News “ How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “|advcl\tin the News “ How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “|prep\tthe|det\tthe News “ How COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “|pobj\t“|punct\tHow|advmod\tVaccine|compound\tAre|auxpass\tHow COVID-19 Vaccine Trials Are Rigged “|appos\t“|punct\t,|punct\ta|det\t“|punct\t”|punct\ta “ successful ” vaccine|nsubj\tonly|advmod\tto|aux\tthe|det\tof symptoms|prep\tsymptoms|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19 Vaccine Trials?",
                    "score": 0.7805,
                    "answers": "Vaccine Trials|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.748,
                    "answers": "COVID-19|npadvmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's not even about reducing infection, hospitalization, or death rates.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that it's not even about reducing infection, hospitalization, or death rates?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the mortality rate of HIV and TB?",
                    "score": 0.7493,
                    "answers": "not|neg\teven|advmod\t,|punct\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the death rate in Denmark in 2020?",
                    "score": 0.7033,
                    "answers": "hospitalization , or death|conj\tinfection , hospitalization , or death rates|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between reducing infection, hospitalization, or death rates?",
                    "score": 0.7021,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that It 's not even about reducing infection , hospitalization , or death rates|ROOT\tthat It 's not even about reducing infection , hospitalization , or death rates|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "ADE in dengue infections Dengue virus is also known to cause ADE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said ADE in dengue infections?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What causes ADE in dengue infections?",
                    "score": 0.7884,
                    "answers": "that ADE in dengue infections Dengue virus is also known to cause ADE|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What causes ADE?",
                    "score": 0.7502,
                    "answers": "to cause ADE|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between ADE and Dengue virus?",
                    "score": 0.7161,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that ADE in dengue infections Dengue virus is also known to cause ADE|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tis|auxpass\talso|advmod\tto|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As explained in a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020:“(..) the pathogenesis of COVID-19 is currently supposed to occur through direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "In what publication was a news report about COVID-19 published?",
                    "answer": "Swiss Medical Weekly"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What kind of mechanisms is the pathogenesis of COVID-19 supposed to occur through?",
                    "answer": "cytotoxic and immunological"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the pathogenesis of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7155,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that As explained in a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020 : “ ( .. ) the pathogenesis of COVID-19 is currently supposed to occur through direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAs|mark\tAs explained in a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020|advcl\tin a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020|prep\ta|det\tnews|compound\ta news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020|pobj\tpublished in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020|acl\tthe|det\tSwiss|compound\tMedical|compound\tin April 2020|prep\t2020|nummod\t:|punct\t“|punct\t(|punct\t..|punct\t)|punct\tthe|det\tthe pathogenesis of COVID-19|nsubjpass\tof COVID-19|prep\tCOVID-19|pobj\tis|auxpass\tcurrently|advmod\tthat As explained in a news report published in the Swiss Medical Weekly in April 2020 : “ ( .. ) the pathogenesis of COVID-19 is currently supposed to occur through direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms|ccomp\tto|aux\tto occur through direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms|xcomp\tthrough direct cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms|prep\tdirect|amod\tcytotoxic and immunological|amod\tand|cc\timmunological|conj\tdirect cytotoxic and immunological mechanisms|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "An additional mechanism that facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage may be called antibody-dependent amplification (ADE).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "answer": "antibody-dependent amplification"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "score": 0.6507,
                    "answers": "the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of antibody-dependent amplification?",
                    "score": 0.632,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that An additional mechanism that facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage may be called antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE )|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tAn|det\tadditional|amod\tAn additional mechanism that facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage|nsubjpass\tthat|nsubj\tthat facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage|relcl\tthe|det\tof virus cells|prep\tvirus|compound\tvirus cells|pobj\tand|cc\tsubsequent|amod\tsubsequent damage|conj\tmay|aux\tbe|auxpass\tantibody|npadvmod\t-|punct\tantibody - dependent|amod\t(|punct\t)|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6012,
                    "answers": "that An additional mechanism that facilitates the entry of virus cells and subsequent damage may be called antibody - dependent amplification ( ADE )|ccomp\tantibody - dependent amplification ( ADE )|oprd\tADE|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "ADE is a known cascade of events in which viruses can infect susceptible cells by interaction between virions complexed with antibodies or complement components and Fc or complement receptors, leading to increased replication.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did 2020news.de say about ADE?",
                    "answer": "ADE is a known cascade of events in which viruses can infect susceptible cells"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many viruses can infect susceptible cells by interaction between virions complexed with antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.8302,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the complement components of ADE?",
                    "score": 0.7308,
                    "answers": "complement components|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies and complement components?",
                    "score": 0.7049,
                    "answers": "antibodies or complement components|pobj\tcomplement|compound\tcomplement|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6775,
                    "answers": "susceptible|amod\tsusceptible cells|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This phenomenon is of enormous importance not only for the understanding of viral pathogenesis, but also for the development of antiviral strategies, in particular vaccines.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that this phenomenon was of enormous importance for the development of antiviral strategies?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the role of vaccines in the development of antiviral strategies?",
                    "score": 0.7985,
                    "answers": "in particular vaccines|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of viral pathogenesis on vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7941,
                    "answers": "This phenomenon|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is viral pathogenesis?",
                    "score": 0.7628,
                    "answers": "of viral pathogenesis|prep\tviral|amod\tviral pathogenesis|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the importance of the study of viral pathogenesis?",
                    "score": 0.7551,
                    "answers": "that This phenomenon is of enormous importance not only for the understanding of viral pathogenesis , but also for the development of antiviral strategies , in particular vaccines|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of an antiviral strategy?",
                    "score": 0.7533,
                    "answers": "antiviral|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "(..)There are four dengue virus serotypes, all of which produce protective immunity.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that there are four dengue virus serotypes?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many serotypes of dengue virus are there?",
                    "answer": "four"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many dengue virus serotypes are there?",
                    "score": 0.8031,
                    "answers": "2020news.de|nsubj\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tdengue|compound\tdengue virus|compound\tof which|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Although homotypic protection is durable, cross neutralising antibodies against different serotypes are short-lived and can only last up to 2 years.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long can cross neutralising antibodies last?",
                    "answer": "2 years"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long is cross neutralizing antibodies against different serotypes?",
                    "score": 0.7233,
                    "answers": "homotypic|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In dengue fever, re-infection with another serotype is more severe when the concentration of protective antibodies decreases.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is more severe in dengue fever when the concentration of protective antibodies decreases?",
                    "answer": "re-infection with another serotype"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How severe is re-infection with another serotype?",
                    "score": 0.8264,
                    "answers": "more severe|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many serotype are there in dengue fever?",
                    "score": 0.7761,
                    "answers": "In dengue fever|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the concentration of protective antibodies in dengue fever?",
                    "score": 0.7599,
                    "answers": "the concentration of protective antibodies|nsubj\tprotective|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of re-infection with another serotype in dengue fever?",
                    "score": 0.7459,
                    "answers": "infection with another serotype|nsubj\tanother serotype|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is dengue fever?",
                    "score": 0.732,
                    "answers": "dengue|compound\tdengue fever|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Here, non-neutralizing antibodies overlap neutralizers, bind to dengue virus virions, and these complexes mediate phagocyte cell infection through interaction with the Fc receptor, in a typical ADE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that non-neutralizing antibodies overlap neutralizers?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How do non-neutralizing antibodies overlap neutralizers, bind to dengue virus virions?",
                    "score": 0.7994,
                    "answers": "these complexes|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are non-neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.6972,
                    "answers": "non - neutralizing antibodies|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between neutralizing antibodies and dengue virus virions?",
                    "score": 0.6942,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tto dengue virus virions|prep\tdengue|compound\tdengue virus|compound\tdengue virus virions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a phagocyte cell infection?",
                    "score": 0.6151,
                    "answers": "a typical ADE|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Fc receptor?",
                    "score": 0.614,
                    "answers": "the Fc receptor|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In other words, heterotypic antibodies at subneutralizing concentrations are responsible for ADE in individuals infected with a dengue virus serotype different from the initial infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is responsible for ADE in individuals infected with a dengue virus serotype different from the initial infection?",
                    "answer": "heterotypic antibodies at subneutralizing concentrations"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of heterotypic antibodies at subneutralizing concentrations in individuals infected with a dengue virus serotype?",
                    "score": 0.7528,
                    "answers": "different from the initial infection|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between subneutralizing concentrations and Dengue virus serotype?",
                    "score": 0.6891,
                    "answers": "at subneutralizing concentrations|prep\tsubneutralizing concentrations|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Cross-reaction neutralising antibodies are associated with a lower probability of symptomatic secondary infection and the higher the concentration of those antibodies after primary infection, the greater the delay in symptomatic secondary infection (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said Cross-reaction neutralising antibodies are associated with a lower probability of symptomatic secondary infection?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Cross-reaction neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.754,
                    "answers": "Cross - reaction neutralising antibodies|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a reaction neutralizing antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7349,
                    "answers": "reaction neutralising|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of cross reaction neutralizing antibodies on the delay in symptomatic secondary infection?",
                    "score": 0.7031,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Cross - reaction neutralising antibodies are associated with a lower probability of symptomatic secondary infection and the higher the concentration of those antibodies after primary infection , the greater the delay in symptomatic secondary infection ( .. )|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between cross-reaction neutralizing antibodies and secondary infection?",
                    "score": 0.6991,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tCross|amod\t-|amod\treaction|npadvmod\tare|auxpass\ta|det\tlower|amod\tsecondary|amod\tand|cc\tthe|advmod\tthe higher|amod\tthe|det\tthe higher the concentration of those antibodies after primary infection|advcl\tof those antibodies|prep\tthose|det\tthose antibodies|pobj\tafter primary infection|prep\tprimary|amod\tprimary infection|pobj\t,|punct\tthe|advmod\tthe|det\tsecondary|amod\t(|punct\t..|punct\t)|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“The document further examines the detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow-up studies, which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non-vaccinated control group.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the document further examines the detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow-up studies?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the rate of dengue hospitalization in vaccinated children under 9 years of age?",
                    "score": 0.7659,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ The document further examines the detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow - up studies , which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t“|punct\tThe|det\tThe document|nsubj\tfurther|advmod\tthat “ The document further examines the detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow - up studies , which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|ccomp\tthe|det\tdetailed|amod\tthe detailed results of the dengue vaccine follow - up studies , which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|dobj\tof the dengue vaccine follow - up studies , which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|prep\tthe|det\tdengue|compound\tdengue vaccine|compound\tfollow|compound\t-|punct\tfollow - up|compound\tthe dengue vaccine follow - up studies , which showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|pobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich showed that the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|relcl\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe rate of dengue hospitalization|nsubj\tof dengue hospitalization|prep\tdengue|compound\tdengue hospitalization|pobj\tthat the rate of dengue hospitalization was higher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|ccomp\thigher in vaccinated children under 9 years of age than in the non - vaccinated control group|acomp\tin vaccinated children under 9 years of age|prep\tvaccinated|amod\tvaccinated children under 9 years of age|pobj\t9|nummod\t9 years of age|pobj\tof age|prep\tage|pobj\tthan in the non - vaccinated control group|prep\tin the non - vaccinated control group|prep\tthe|det\tnon|amod\t-|amod\tvaccinated|amod\tcontrol|compound\tthe non - vaccinated control group|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The explanation for this seems to be that the vaccine imitated a primary infection, and as this immunity weakened, the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the explanation for this?",
                    "answer": "the vaccine imitated a primary infection, and as this immunity weakened, the children became susceptible to ADE"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many times did children become susceptible to ADE?",
                    "score": 0.777,
                    "answers": "the second time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the virus do to the children who became susceptible to ADE?",
                    "score": 0.759,
                    "answers": "as this immunity weakened|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many children were susceptible to ADE after they met the virus?",
                    "score": 0.7441,
                    "answers": "that The explanation for this seems to be that the vaccine imitated a primary infection , and as this immunity weakened , the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time|ccomp\tthat the vaccine imitated a primary infection , and as this immunity weakened , the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of the children becoming susceptible to ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6964,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The explanation for this seems to be that the vaccine imitated a primary infection , and as this immunity weakened , the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time|ROOT\tto be that the vaccine imitated a primary infection , and as this immunity weakened , the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time|xcomp\tas this immunity weakened , the children became susceptible to ADE when they met the virus for the second time|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the explanation for the virus being susceptible to ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6908,
                    "answers": "The explanation for this|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The author explains:“A post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test to distinguish antibodies caused by a wild-type infection that occurred after vaccination showed that the vaccine could protect against severe dengue [in] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination and that the risk of a serious clinical outcome increased in seronegative individuals.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of individuals increased the risk of a serious clinical outcome?",
                    "answer": "seronegative"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did an ELISA test do to determine antibodies caused by wild-type infection?",
                    "score": 0.821,
                    "answers": "post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test to distinguish antibodies caused by a wild - type infection that occurred after vaccination showed that the vaccine could protect against severe dengue [ in ] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination and that the risk of a serious clinical outcome increased in seronegative individuals|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did a post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test show?",
                    "score": 0.8189,
                    "answers": "post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test to distinguish antibodies caused by a wild - type infection that occurred after vaccination|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the author say about the ELISA test?",
                    "score": 0.7645,
                    "answers": "that The author explains:“A|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seronegative individuals were exposed to severe dengue?",
                    "score": 0.7403,
                    "answers": "seronegative individuals|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the ELISA test show?",
                    "score": 0.739,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The author explains:“A post hoc analysis of efficacy trials using an ELISA test to distinguish antibodies caused by a wild - type infection that occurred after vaccination showed that the vaccine could protect against severe dengue [ in ] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination and that the risk of a serious clinical outcome increased in seronegative individuals|ROOT\tthat the vaccine could protect against severe dengue [ in ] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination and that the risk of a serious clinical outcome increased in seronegative individuals|advcl\tagainst severe dengue [ in ] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination|prep\tsevere dengue [ in ] individuals exposed to natural infection prior to vaccination|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "On this basis, a strategic expert group convened by the World Health Organization (WHO) concluded that only dengue-positive individuals should be vaccinated if dengue control programmes including vaccination are planned.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that a strategic expert group convened by the World Health Organization (WHO) concluded that only dengue-positive individuals should be vaccinated?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the WHO say about dengue control programs?",
                    "score": 0.8162,
                    "answers": "the World Health Organization ( WHO )|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the World Health Organization say about dengue-positive individuals being vaccinated?",
                    "score": 0.8052,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“ADE in Coronavirus InfectionsThis may ultimately be relevant for the COVID-19 vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that ADE in Coronavirus Infections may ultimately be relevant for the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are Coronavirus Infections?",
                    "score": 0.7975,
                    "answers": "Coronavirus|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7896,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ ADE in Coronavirus InfectionsThis may ultimately be relevant for the COVID-19 vaccine|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t“|punct\tmay|aux\tultimately|advmod\tthat “ ADE in Coronavirus InfectionsThis may ultimately be relevant for the COVID-19 vaccine|ccomp\trelevant for the COVID-19 vaccine|acomp\tfor the COVID-19 vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tCOVID-19|nmod\tthe COVID-19 vaccine|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the Coronavirus Infections?",
                    "score": 0.7686,
                    "answers": "ADE in Coronavirus InfectionsThis|nsubj\tin Coronavirus InfectionsThis|prep\tCoronavirus InfectionsThis|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Hypothetically speaking: If SARS-CoV-2 acts like dengue, which is also caused by an RNA virus, then anyone who is not positive in the SARS-CoV-2 test could actually have an increased risk of severe COVID-19 after vaccination, and only those who have already recovered from a COVID-19 attack would be protected from severe disease by the vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that if SARS-CoV-2 acts like dengue, who could have an increased risk of severe COVID-19 after vaccination?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people have recovered from a COVID-19 attack?",
                    "score": 0.7485,
                    "answers": "only those who have already recovered from a COVID-19 attack|nsubjpass\twho have already recovered from a COVID-19 attack|relcl\tonly those who have already recovered from a COVID-19 attack would be protected from severe disease by the vaccine|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the risk of COVID-19 after vaccination?",
                    "score": 0.737,
                    "answers": "severe|amod\tCOVID-19|nummod\tsevere|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.7103,
                    "answers": "25/11/2020|pobj\tHypothetically speaking :|advcl\tSARS|compound\tSARS - CoV-2|nsubj\tIf SARS - CoV-2 acts like dengue , which is also caused by an RNA virus|advcl\tlike dengue , which is also caused by an RNA virus|prep\tdengue , which is also caused by an RNA virus|pobj\twhich is also caused by an RNA virus|relcl\tby an RNA virus|agent\tRNA|compound\tanyone who is not positive in the SARS - CoV-2 test|nsubj\twho is not positive in the SARS - CoV-2 test|relcl\tin the SARS - CoV-2 test|prep\tSARS|compound\tSARS - CoV-2|compound\tthe SARS - CoV-2 test|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between SARS-CoV-2 and Dengue?",
                    "score": 0.7035,
                    "answers": "Hypothetically|advmod\tan RNA virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Let's be clear:We don't know if this is the case or not, but these are important areas of research and the ongoing vaccine studies simply won't be able to answer this important question.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What will not be able to answer this important question?",
                    "answer": "vaccine studies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the research on vaccines and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7135,
                    "answers": "that Let 's be clear : We do n't know if this is the case or not , but these are important areas of research and the ongoing vaccine studies simply wo n't be able to answer this important question|ccomp\tthese are important areas of research and the ongoing vaccine studies simply wo n't be able to answer this important question|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does 2020news.de say about vaccines and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7088,
                    "answers": "'s be clear|ccomp\tdo|aux\tor|cc\t,|punct\tthese|nsubj\timportant areas of research|attr\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of research on vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.706,
                    "answers": "of research|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between vaccines and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.6974,
                    "answers": "clear|acomp\tif this is the case or not|ccomp\tnot|conj\tbut|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the question of vaccines and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.6966,
                    "answers": "able to answer this important question|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The Swiss Medical Weekly document also examines ADE tests on coronavirus infections and cites research that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV (feline infectious peritonitis virus) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does vaccination of cats against FIPV do?",
                    "answer": "increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is FIPV serotype?",
                    "score": 0.6706,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The Swiss Medical Weekly document also examines ADE tests on coronavirus infections and cites research that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|ROOT\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tSwiss|compound\talso|advmod\tthat The Swiss Medical Weekly document also examines ADE tests on coronavirus infections and cites research that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|ccomp\tADE tests on coronavirus infections|dobj\tcites research that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|conj\tresearch that shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|dobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat shows that vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|relcl\tthat|mark\t(|punct\tthat vaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus – increases the severity of the disease when it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe|det\twhen|advmod\tis|auxpass\twhen it is found with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|advcl\tthe|det\tsame|amod\tthe|det\tcontained in the vaccine|acl\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is FIPV?",
                    "score": 0.6684,
                    "answers": "2020news.de|nsubj\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tMedical|compound\tThe Swiss Medical Weekly document|nsubj\tADE|compound\ton coronavirus infections|prep\tcoronavirus|compound\tcoronavirus infections|pobj\tand|cc\tvaccination of cats against FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus –|nsubj\tof cats|prep\tcats|pobj\tagainst FIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus –|prep\tFIPV ( feline infectious peritonitis virus ) – a feline coronavirus –|pobj\tfeline|amod\tinfectious|amod\tperitonitis|compound\tfeline infectious peritonitis virus|appos\t)|punct\t–|punct\ta|det\tfeline|amod\ta feline coronavirus|appos\t–|punct\tof the disease|prep\tthe disease|pobj\tit|nsubjpass\tFIPV|compound\tin the vaccine|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the severity of FIPV?",
                    "score": 0.667,
                    "answers": "the severity of the disease|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the FIPV serotype?",
                    "score": 0.6633,
                    "answers": "with the same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|prep\tthe same FIPV serotype as the serotype contained in the vaccine|pobj\tas the serotype contained in the vaccine|prep\tthe serotype contained in the vaccine|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“Experiments have shown that immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induced lung immunopathology when exposed to SARS virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induce when exposed to SARS virus?",
                    "answer": "lung immunopathology"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many SARS vaccines have been exposed to SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.8147,
                    "answers": "that “ Experiments have shown that immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induced lung immunopathology when exposed to SARS virus|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of immunization with SARS vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7786,
                    "answers": "Experiments|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.7179,
                    "answers": "when exposed to SARS virus|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS?",
                    "score": 0.6863,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that “ Experiments have shown that immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induced lung immunopathology when exposed to SARS virus|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t“|punct\tthat|mark\ta|det\tof SARS vaccines|prep\tSARS|compound\tSARS vaccines|pobj\tthat immunization with a variety of SARS vaccines induced lung immunopathology when exposed to SARS virus|ccomp\tlung|compound\tlung immunopathology|dobj\twhen|advmod\tto SARS virus|prep\tSARS|compound\tSARS virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“The paper also cites research showing that “the antibodies induced by a vaccine against SARS-CoV amplify infection of B cell lines despite the protective reactions of the hamster model”.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the paper cites research showing that antibodies induced by a vaccine against SARS-CoV amplify infection of B cell lines?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of virus is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.8305,
                    "answers": "hamster|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the research show about SARS-CoV amplify infection of B cell lines?",
                    "score": 0.8219,
                    "answers": "that “ The paper also cites research showing that “ the antibodies induced by a vaccine against SARS - CoV amplify infection of B cell lines despite the protective reactions of the hamster model|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who created the hamster model?",
                    "score": 0.7584,
                    "answers": "the hamster model|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the protective reactions of the hamster model?",
                    "score": 0.721,
                    "answers": "protective|amod\tthe protective reactions of the hamster model|pobj\tof the hamster model|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7168,
                    "answers": "The paper|nsubj\tthe antibodies induced by a vaccine against SARS - CoV|nsubj\tinduced by a vaccine against SARS - CoV|acl\tby a vaccine against SARS - CoV|agent\ta|det\ta vaccine against SARS - CoV|pobj\tagainst SARS - CoV|prep\tSARS|compound\tSARS - CoV|pobj\tof B cell lines|prep\tB cell|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In another document, published in 2014, it was found that antibody-dependent SARS coronavirus infection is mediated by antibodies against puncture proteins:“(..) the highest levels of antisera against SARS-CoV neutralized SARS-CoV infection, while highly diluted antisera significantly increased SARS-CoV infection and induced higher levels of apoptosis.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that antibody-dependent SARS coronavirus infection is mediated by antibodies against puncture proteins?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What significantly increased SARS-CoV infection and induced higher levels of apoptosis?",
                    "answer": "highly diluted antisera"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the levels of antisera against SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7468,
                    "answers": "against puncture proteins|prep\tof apoptosis|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies against SARS coronavirus and SARS?",
                    "score": 0.7231,
                    "answers": "that In another document , published in 2014 , it was found that antibody - dependent SARS coronavirus infection is mediated by antibodies against puncture proteins|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS coronavirus?",
                    "score": 0.7095,
                    "answers": "antibody - dependent SARS coronavirus infection|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.6968,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tanother document , published in 2014 ,|pobj\tSARS|compound\tSARS coronavirus|compound\tSARS|compound\tSARS|compound\tSARS - CoV infection|dobj\tSARS|compound\tSARS - CoV infection|dobj\tapoptosis|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Infectiousity test results indicate that SARS-CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did 2020news.de say about SARS-CoV ADE?",
                    "answer": "Infectiousity test results indicate that SARS-CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV ADE?",
                    "score": 0.6733,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Infectiousity test results indicate that SARS - CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tInfectiousity|compound\ttest|compound\tInfectiousity test results|nsubj\tthat Infectiousity test results indicate that SARS - CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|ccomp\tthat|mark\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|compound\tSARS - CoV ADE|nsubjpass\tis|auxpass\tthat SARS - CoV ADE is mediated mainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|ccomp\tmainly|advmod\tmainly by diluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|agent\tdiluted|amod\tdiluted antibodies against peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|pobj\tagainst peak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|prep\tpeak|compound\tpeak envelope|compound\tpeak envelope proteins rather than nucleocapside proteins|pobj\trather|advmod\trather than nucleocapside proteins|cc\tnucleocapside|compound\tnucleocapside proteins|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We also generated monoclonal antibodies against SARS-CoV tip proteins and observed that most of them promoted SARS-CoV infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did we generate monoclonal antibodies against?",
                    "answer": "SARS-CoV tip proteins"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many monoclonal antibodies did SARS-CoV tip proteins produce?",
                    "score": 0.784,
                    "answers": "most of them|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are SARS-CoV tip proteins?",
                    "score": 0.7652,
                    "answers": "against SARS - CoV tip proteins|prep\tSARS - CoV tip proteins|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many SARS-CoV tip proteins are there?",
                    "score": 0.7621,
                    "answers": "of them|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV tip proteins?",
                    "score": 0.7398,
                    "answers": "monoclonal antibodies against SARS - CoV tip proteins|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7254,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that We also generated monoclonal antibodies against SARS - CoV tip proteins and observed that most of them promoted SARS - CoV infection|ROOT\tthat We also generated monoclonal antibodies against SARS - CoV tip proteins and observed that most of them promoted SARS - CoV infection|ccomp\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|compound\tSARS - CoV tip|compound\tand|cc\tthat most of them promoted SARS - CoV infection|ccomp\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|compound\tSARS - CoV infection|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Overall, our results suggest that antibodies to SARS-CoV tip proteins can trigger the effects of ADE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that our results suggest that antibodies to SARS-CoV tip proteins can trigger the effects of ADE?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does SARS-CoV tip proteins do to cause ADE?",
                    "score": 0.767,
                    "answers": "the|det\tof ADE|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of SARS-CoV tip proteins?",
                    "score": 0.7442,
                    "answers": "to SARS - CoV tip proteins|prep\tSARS|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies to SARS-CoV tip proteins and ADE?",
                    "score": 0.7329,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Overall , our results suggest that antibodies to SARS - CoV tip proteins can trigger the effects of ADE|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tADE|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV tip proteins?",
                    "score": 0.7301,
                    "answers": "antibodies to SARS - CoV tip proteins|nsubj\tSARS - CoV|compound\tSARS - CoV tip proteins|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of SARS-CoV tip proteins on ADE?",
                    "score": 0.714,
                    "answers": "that Overall , our results suggest that antibodies to SARS - CoV tip proteins can trigger the effects of ADE|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The data raises new questions about a possible vaccine against SARS-CoV (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said the data raises new questions about a possible vaccine against SARS-CoV?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the possible vaccine against SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.8136,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The data raises new questions about a possible vaccine against SARS - CoV ( .. )|ROOT\tthat The data raises new questions about a possible vaccine against SARS - CoV|ccomp\tnew questions about a possible vaccine against SARS - CoV|dobj\tabout a possible vaccine against SARS - CoV|prep\tpossible|amod\ta possible vaccine against SARS - CoV|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7534,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tThe data|nsubj\tnew|amod\ta|det\tagainst SARS - CoV|prep\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|pobj\t(|punct\t..|punct\t)|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7452,
                    "answers": "2020news.de|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“A study following this was published in the JCI Insight magazine in 2019.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What magazine did 2020news.de say a study was published in in 2019?",
                    "answer": "JCI Insight"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who published the JCI Insight magazine in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.6755,
                    "answers": "JCI|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the study published in the JCI Insight magazine?",
                    "score": 0.6388,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Here, macaques vaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus (MVA), which encodes SARS-CoV tip protein of full length, ended up with a more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did macaques vaccinated with the MVA end up with than animals exposed to the SARS virus?",
                    "answer": "more severe lung pathology"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How severe is SARS-CoV tip protein?",
                    "score": 0.7794,
                    "answers": "more severe|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.6835,
                    "answers": "lung|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does MVA stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6763,
                    "answers": "SARS|compound\tSARS - CoV|compound\tSARS - CoV tip|compound\tSARS - CoV tip protein of full length|dobj\tthan animals exposed to SARS virus|prep\tanimals exposed to SARS virus|pobj\texposed to SARS virus|acl\tSARS|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between MVA and SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.6595,
                    "answers": "modified|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MVA?",
                    "score": 0.6524,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Here , macaques vaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length , ended up with a more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus|ROOT\tthat|mark\tHere|advmod\t,|punct\tmacaques vaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length ,|nsubj\tvaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length ,|acl\twith a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length ,|prep\ta|det\tVaccinia|compound\tVaccinia Ankara|compound\ta modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length ,|pobj\t(|punct\tMVA|appos\t)|punct\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length|relcl\t-|punct\tof full length|prep\tfull|amod\tfull length|pobj\t,|punct\tthat Here , macaques vaccinated with a modified Vaccinia Ankara virus ( MVA ) , which encodes SARS - CoV tip protein of full length , ended up with a more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus|ccomp\twith a more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus|prep\ta|det\tmore|advmod\ta more severe lung pathology than animals exposed to SARS virus|pobj\tto SARS virus|prep\tSARS virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And when they transferred IgG anti-spike antibodies to unvaccinated macaques, they developed acute diffuse alveolar damage, probably because of “distorting the resolution response of inflammation”.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that when they transferred IgG anti-spike antibodies to unvaccinated macaques, they developed acute diffuse alveolar damage?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between IgG anti-spike antibodies and acute diffuse alveolar damage?",
                    "score": 0.7256,
                    "answers": "IgG anti - spike antibodies|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the resolution response to inflammation?",
                    "score": 0.643,
                    "answers": "And|cc\t-|amod\tunvaccinated|amod\tacute|amod\tdiffuse|amod\talveolar|amod\tof|pcomp\tthe|det\tresolution|compound\tof inflammation|prep\tinflammation|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The SARS vaccine aggravates infection after infection with SARS-CoVAn interesting 2012 news story with the revealing title “Immunization with SARS Coronavirus Vaccines Leads to Pulmonary Immunopathology on Challenge with the SARS Virus” shows what many researchers now fear, namely that COVID-19 vaccines can make people more susceptible to serious SARS-CoV-2 infections.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What can make people more susceptible to serious SARS-CoV-2 infections?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19 vaccines"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does COVID-19 vaccines do to prevent SARS-CoV2?",
                    "score": 0.8675,
                    "answers": "can|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does COVID-19 Vaccine do to prevent SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.8582,
                    "answers": "Coronavirus|compound\twhat|dobj\tSARS - CoV-2|nmod\tserious SARS - CoV-2 infections|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many researchers fear COVID-19 vaccines can make people more susceptible to serious SARS-CoV2 infections?",
                    "score": 0.8391,
                    "answers": "many researchers|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19 Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8014,
                    "answers": "interesting 2012 news story with the revealing title “ Immunization with SARS Coronavirus Vaccines Leads to Pulmonary Immunopathology on Challenge with the SARS Virus ” shows what many researchers now fear , namely that COVID-19 vaccines can make people more susceptible to serious SARS - CoV-2 infections|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the SARS Coronavirus Vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7882,
                    "answers": "with the revealing title “|prep\tSARS Coronavirus Vaccines|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The paper provides an overview of experiments that show that immunization with various vaccines against SARS resulted in lung immunopathology that eventually faced SARS virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did immunization with SARS vaccines result in?",
                    "answer": "lung immunopathology"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the study show about SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.7798,
                    "answers": "that The paper provides an overview of experiments that show that immunization with various vaccines against SARS resulted in lung immunopathology that eventually faced SARS virus|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the effect of immunization with various vaccines against SARS?",
                    "score": 0.7658,
                    "answers": "experiments that show that immunization with various vaccines against SARS resulted in lung immunopathology that eventually faced SARS virus|pobj\tthat immunization with various vaccines against SARS resulted in lung immunopathology that eventually faced SARS virus|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the result of the SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.7388,
                    "answers": "eventually|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS virus?",
                    "score": 0.6997,
                    "answers": "that eventually faced SARS virus|relcl\tSARS virus|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the effects of SARS on lung immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6976,
                    "answers": "The paper|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As the authors pointed out:“Inactivated vaccines against the whole virus, whether inactivated with formalin or beta-propylactone and administered with or without alum adjuvant, showed an immunopathological type Th2 in the lungs after the challenge.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What were the two vaccines that were inactivated with?",
                    "answer": "formalin or beta-propylactone"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the authors say about Inactivated vaccines against the whole virus?",
                    "score": 0.7989,
                    "answers": "As the authors pointed|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the effect of Inactivated Vaccine on the lungs?",
                    "score": 0.7184,
                    "answers": "out:“Inactivated|punct\tagainst the whole virus|prep\tthe challenge|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Inactivated vaccines and beta-propylactone?",
                    "score": 0.6933,
                    "answers": "the authors|nsubj\twhether|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the beta-propylactone?",
                    "score": 0.6642,
                    "answers": "beta|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is propylactone?",
                    "score": 0.6569,
                    "answers": "propylactone|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As mentioned above, immunopathology was attributed in two reports to the presence of protein N in the vaccine; however, the same immunopathological response was found in animals to which only the S-protein vaccine was administered, although it appeared to be less intense.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was different about the animals that were given the S-protein vaccine?",
                    "answer": "same immunopathological response was found in animals to which only the S-protein vaccine was administered, although it appeared to be less intense"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the presence of protein N in the S-protein vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7577,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tAs|mark\tAs mentioned above|advcl\t,|punct\twas|auxpass\tin two reports|prep\ttwo reports|pobj\tthe|det\tof protein N|prep\tin the vaccine|prep\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|pobj\t;|punct\thowever|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\timmunopathological|amod\twas|auxpass\tthat As mentioned above , immunopathology was attributed in two reports to the presence of protein N in the vaccine ; however , the same immunopathological response was found in animals to which only the S - protein vaccine was administered , although it appeared to be less intense|ccomp\tto which|prep\twhich|pobj\tonly|advmod\tthe|det\tS|compound\t-|punct\twas|auxpass\tto which only the S - protein vaccine was administered|relcl\t,|punct\talthough|mark\tit|nsubj\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many animals received the S-protein vaccine in 2020?",
                    "score": 0.7527,
                    "answers": "in animals to which only the S - protein vaccine was administered|prep\tanimals to which only the S - protein vaccine was administered|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of the S-protein vaccine on immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7491,
                    "answers": "to be less intense|xcomp\tless intense|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between S-protein vaccine and immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.723,
                    "answers": "the same immunopathological response|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7005,
                    "answers": "immunopathology|nsubjpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Thus, an immunopathological response of type Th2 to the infection of vaccinated animals occurred in three of the four animal models (not in hamsters), including two different strains of mice endogamous with four different types of vaccines against SARS-CoV with and without alum adjuvant.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many different strains of mice were vaccinated against SARS-CoV with and without alum adjuvant?",
                    "answer": "two different strains of mice endogamous with four different types of vaccines against SARS-CoV"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of vaccines does SARS-CoV contain?",
                    "score": 0.8584,
                    "answers": "of mice endogamous with four different types of vaccines against SARS - CoV with and without alum adjuvant|prep\tof vaccines against SARS - CoV|prep\tvaccines against SARS - CoV|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of immunopathological response does  Th2 have to the infection of vaccinated animals?",
                    "score": 0.8335,
                    "answers": "type Th2|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What animals have an immunopathological response of type Th2?",
                    "score": 0.8023,
                    "answers": "hamsters|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many types of vaccines are available against SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.765,
                    "answers": "four different types of vaccines against SARS - CoV with and without alum adjuvant|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many different types of vaccines against SARS-CoV are available?",
                    "score": 0.7386,
                    "answers": "two different strains of mice endogamous with four different types of vaccines against SARS - CoV with and without alum adjuvant|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "No inactivated vaccine preparation has been reported to induce this result in non-human mice, ferrets and primates.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that no inactivated vaccine preparation was reported to induce this result in non-human mice, ferrets and primates?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many inactivated vaccines has there been?",
                    "score": 0.8055,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many inactivated vaccine preparation has there been for non-human mice, ferrets and primates?",
                    "score": 0.8024,
                    "answers": "ferrets and primates|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of inactivated vaccine preparation on humans?",
                    "score": 0.7699,
                    "answers": "has|aux\tto|aux\tnon|amod\t-|amod\thuman|amod\t,|punct\tand|cc\tprimates|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is inactivated vaccine preparation?",
                    "score": 0.7518,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that No inactivated vaccine preparation has been reported to induce this result in non - human mice , ferrets and primates|ROOT\tinactivated|amod\tNo inactivated vaccine preparation|nsubjpass\tthat No inactivated vaccine preparation has been reported to induce this result in non - human mice , ferrets and primates|ccomp\tto induce this result in non - human mice , ferrets and primates|advcl\tin non - human mice , ferrets and primates|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are non-human animals?",
                    "score": 0.7008,
                    "answers": "non - human mice , ferrets and primates|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Taken together, these experiences give rise to concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS-CoV in humans.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that these experiences give rise to concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS-CoV in humans?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7283,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Taken together , these experiences give rise to concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tTaken together|advcl\ttogether|advmod\t,|punct\tthese|det\tthese experiences|nsubj\trise|dobj\tto concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|prep\tconcern about the trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|pobj\tabout the trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|prep\tthe|det\tthe trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|pobj\tof vaccines against SARS - CoV|prep\tvaccines against SARS - CoV|pobj\tagainst SARS - CoV|prep\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV|pobj\tin humans|prep\thumans|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of SARS-CoV in humans?",
                    "score": 0.7234,
                    "answers": "that Taken together , these experiences give rise to concern about the trials of vaccines against SARS - CoV in humans|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Clinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines have been conducted which have been reported to induce antibody responses and are ‘safe'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said Clinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines were safe?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are SARS coronavirus vaccines safe?",
                    "score": 0.9109,
                    "answers": "and|cc\tare ‘ safe '|conj\tsafe|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are SARS coronavirus vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.853,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Clinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines have been conducted which have been reported to induce antibody responses and are ‘ safe '|ROOT\tthat|mark\tof SARS coronavirus vaccines|prep\tSARS coronavirus vaccines|pobj\thave|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tthat Clinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines have been conducted which have been reported to induce antibody responses and are ‘ safe '|ccomp\twhich|nsubjpass\thave|aux\tbeen|auxpass\twhich have been reported to induce antibody responses and are ‘ safe '|relcl\tto|aux\tto induce antibody responses and are ‘ safe '|xcomp\tantibody responses|dobj\t‘|punct\t'|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of SARS coronavirus vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8325,
                    "answers": "antibody|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS coronavirus?",
                    "score": 0.7459,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tClinical|amod\tClinical trials of SARS coronavirus vaccines|nsubjpass\tSARS|compound\tSARS coronavirus|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However, the safety test has only been provided for a short observation period.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long has the safety test been provided?",
                    "answer": "a short observation period"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long has the safety test been provided?",
                    "score": 0.6339,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tHowever|advmod\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the safety test?",
                    "score": 0.5262,
                    "answers": "safety|compound\tthe safety test|nsubjpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The concern raised in this report concerns the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS-CoV infectious virus, which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that the concern raised in this report concerns the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS-CoV infectious virus?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people who are exposed to SARS-CoV infectious virus?",
                    "score": 0.7888,
                    "answers": "when they are exposed to SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV infectious virus?",
                    "score": 0.7504,
                    "answers": "that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of SARS-CoV infectious virus?",
                    "score": 0.7306,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The concern raised in this report concerns the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|ROOT\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tin this report|prep\tthis|det\tthat The concern raised in this report concerns the immunopathological response that occurs in vaccinated people when they are exposed to SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|ccomp\tthe|det\tthat|nsubj\tvaccinated|amod\tvaccinated people|pobj\twhen|advmod\tthey|nsubjpass\tare|auxpass\t-|punct\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the basis for the development of the SARS vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7242,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|pobj\twhich forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|relcl\tthe basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|dobj\tthe development of a SARS vaccine|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7166,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tThe concern raised in this report|nsubj\traised in this report|acl\tthis report|pobj\tin vaccinated people|prep\tto SARS - CoV infectious virus , which forms the basis for the development of a SARS vaccine|prep\tSARS|nmod\tSARS - CoV|nmod\tinfectious|amod\tfor the development of a SARS vaccine|prep\tof a SARS vaccine|prep\ta|det\tSARS|compound\ta SARS vaccine|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Other safety concerns relate to the efficacy and safety against antigenic variants of the severe acute respiratory syndrome virus (SARS-CoV) and the safety of people exposed to other krone viruses, in particular those in the type 2 group.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of krone virus is SARS-CoV a part of?",
                    "answer": "type 2"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the safety concerns of people exposed to the severe acute respiratory syndrome virus (SARS-CoV)?",
                    "score": 0.7427,
                    "answers": "against antigenic variants of the severe acute respiratory syndrome virus ( SARS - CoV )|prep\tantigenic variants of the severe acute respiratory syndrome virus ( SARS - CoV )|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“Older people are the most vulnerable to ADEIn addition to all these concerns, there is evidence that older people, who are the most affected by severe COVID-19 diseases, are also the most affected by ADE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of disease affects older people the most?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are older people the most affected by severe COVID-19 diseases?",
                    "score": 0.873,
                    "answers": ", there is evidence that older people , who are the most affected by severe COVID-19 diseases , are also the most affected by ADE|ccomp\tevidence that older people , who are the most affected by severe COVID-19 diseases , are also the most affected by ADE|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "A preliminary investigation published on the medRxiv prepress server at the end of March 2020 reported that middle-aged and elderly patients with COVID-19 have much higher concentrations of anti-spike antibodies – which in turn increase infectivity – than younger patients.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the disease that causes a higher concentration of anti-spike antibodies in middle-aged and elderly patients?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How old are the patients with COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7393,
                    "answers": "younger|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What age group did the medRxiv prepress server belong to?",
                    "score": 0.7254,
                    "answers": "middle - aged and elderly|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7034,
                    "answers": "of anti - spike antibodies|prep\tanti|amod\twhich in turn increase infectivity|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between COVID-19 and infectivity?",
                    "score": 0.7001,
                    "answers": "infectivity|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6725,
                    "answers": "middle - aged and elderly patients with COVID-19|nsubj\twith COVID-19|prep\tCOVID-19|pobj\tthat middle - aged and elderly patients with COVID-19 have much higher concentrations of anti - spike antibodies – which in turn increase infectivity – than younger patients|ccomp\tanti - spike antibodies|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Strengthening Immunity Is a Serious ConcernAnother document worth mentioning is the mini-review of May 2020 “Impact of immune enhancement on Covid-19 polyclonal hyperimmune globulin therapy and vaccine development” (Effects of immune enhancement in polyclonal hyperimmunoglobulin therapy COVID-19 and vaccine development).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is another document worth mentioning?",
                    "answer": "the mini-review of May 2020 “Impact of immune enhancement on Covid-19 polyclonal hyperimmune globulin therapy and vaccine development”"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of immune enhancement on Covid-19?",
                    "score": 0.7692,
                    "answers": "polyclonal hyperimmune globulin therapy and vaccine development|pobj\tvaccine development|conj\tvaccine development|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Covid-19?",
                    "score": 0.7612,
                    "answers": "on Covid-19 polyclonal hyperimmune globulin therapy and vaccine development|prep\tCovid-19|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7612,
                    "answers": "in polyclonal hyperimmunoglobulin therapy COVID-19 and vaccine development|prep\tpolyclonal hyperimmunoglobulin therapy COVID-19 and vaccine development|pobj\tCOVID-19|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of Strengthening Immunity?",
                    "score": 0.7552,
                    "answers": "25/11/2020|pobj\tdocument worth mentioning|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Strengthening immunity and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7538,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As in many other studies, the authors point out that:“While the development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine is promising, both present a common theoretical safety problem.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that As many other studies, the authors point out that:“While hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine are promising, both present a common theoretical safety problem.”",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the safety problems with the SARS-CoV-2 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7562,
                    "answers": "many other studies|pobj\tthat As in many other studies , the authors point out that:“While the development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS - CoV-2 vaccine is promising , both present a common theoretical safety problem|ccomp\tthe development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS - CoV-2 vaccine|nsubj\tthe development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS - CoV-2 vaccine is promising|advcl\tthat:“While the development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS - CoV-2 vaccine is promising , both present a common theoretical safety problem|ccomp\tcommon|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the development of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS-CoV-2 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7419,
                    "answers": "the authors|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the safety problem of the SARS-CoV-2 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7322,
                    "answers": "of hyperimmunoglobulin treatment and SARS - CoV-2 vaccine|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.7019,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tAs in many other studies|prep\tmany|amod\tother|amod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tout|prt\tthat:“While|punct\tthe|det\tand|cc\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV-2|compound\tSARS - CoV-2 vaccine|conj\tpromising|acomp\t,|punct\tboth|nsubj\ta|det\ttheoretical|amod\ta common theoretical safety problem|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Experimental studies have suggested that SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections may increase immunity, which may occur similarly in SARS-CoV-2 infection (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that Experimental studies suggested that SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV infections may increase immunity?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2 infection?",
                    "score": 0.7607,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Experimental studies have suggested that SARS - CoV and MERS - CoV infections may increase immunity , which may occur similarly in SARS - CoV-2 infection ( .. )|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.724,
                    "answers": "MERS|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.723,
                    "answers": "MERS - CoV|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.7189,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tExperimental|amod\tExperimental studies|nsubj\thave|aux\tthat Experimental studies have suggested that SARS - CoV and MERS - CoV infections may increase immunity , which may occur similarly in SARS - CoV-2 infection|ccomp\tthat|mark\tSARS|nmod\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV and MERS - CoV|nmod\tand|cc\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV and MERS - CoV infections|nsubj\tmay|aux\tthat SARS - CoV and MERS - CoV infections may increase immunity , which may occur similarly in SARS - CoV-2 infection|ccomp\timmunity , which may occur similarly in SARS - CoV-2 infection|dobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tmay|aux\twhich may occur similarly in SARS - CoV-2 infection|relcl\tsimilarly|advmod\tin SARS - CoV-2 infection|prep\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV-2|compound\tSARS - CoV-2 infection|pobj\t(|punct\t..|punct\t)|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Theoretically, there are two ways to strengthen the immune increase of the disease.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that there are two ways to strengthen the immune increase of Alzheimer's disease?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many ways to strengthen the immune increase of the disease?",
                    "score": 0.7513,
                    "answers": "of the disease|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "First, non-neutralizing or sub-neutralizing amounts of antibodies can amplify SARS-CoV-2 infection in target cells.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that non-neutralizing or sub-neutralizing amounts of antibodies can amplify SARS-CoV-2 infection in target cells?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of neutralizing or sub-neutralizing amounts of antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.744,
                    "answers": "neutralizing|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the target cells of SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.7214,
                    "answers": "target|compound\ttarget cells|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV-2?",
                    "score": 0.698,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that First , non - neutralizing or sub - neutralizing amounts of antibodies can amplify SARS - CoV-2 infection in target cells|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t,|punct\tnon|amod\t-|amod\tneutralizing or sub - neutralizing|amod\tor|cc\tsub|conj\t-|conj\tnon - neutralizing or sub - neutralizing amounts of antibodies|nsubj\tof antibodies|prep\tantibodies|pobj\tcan|aux\tthat First , non - neutralizing or sub - neutralizing amounts of antibodies can amplify SARS - CoV-2 infection in target cells|ccomp\tSARS|compound\t-|punct\tSARS - CoV-2|compound\tSARS - CoV-2 infection|dobj\tin target cells|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Second, antibodies could increase inflammation and therefore the severity of lung disease.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of disease did 2020news.de say antibodies could increase inflammation?",
                    "answer": "lung disease"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies and the severity of lung disease?",
                    "score": 0.7328,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Second , antibodies could increase inflammation and therefore the severity of lung disease|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\t,|punct\tantibodies|nsubj\tcould|aux\tthat Second , antibodies could increase inflammation and therefore the severity of lung disease|ccomp\tand|cc\ttherefore|advmod\tthe|det\tlung|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of lung disease?",
                    "score": 0.7176,
                    "answers": "of lung disease|prep\tlung disease|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Figure 1 summarizes an overview of these antibody-dependent infectious and immunopathological augmentation effects (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that Figure 1 summarizes an overview of antibody-dependent infectious and immunopathological augmentation effects?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of antibody-dependent infectious and immunopathological augmentation effects?",
                    "score": 0.7336,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\tand|cc\t(|punct\t..|punct\t)|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the immunopathological augmentation effects?",
                    "score": 0.6866,
                    "answers": "infectious and immunopathological|amod\timmunopathological|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Several candidates for SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV vaccine are currently in initial preclinical or clinical trials.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that several candidates for SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV vaccine are currently in initial preclinical or clinical trials?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the candidates for SARS-CoV and MERS- CoV vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8215,
                    "answers": "SARS - CoV and MERS - CoV|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many candidates for the SARS-CoV vaccine are currently in initial preclinical or clinical trials?",
                    "score": 0.8215,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tinitial|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the SARS-CoV vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7901,
                    "answers": "for SARS - CoV and MERS - CoV vaccine|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is MERS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.764,
                    "answers": "MERS|compound\tMERS - CoV|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SARS-CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7582,
                    "answers": "SARS|nmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Animal studies on these CoVs have shown that vaccines based on protein S (especially receptor binding domain, RBD) are highly immunogenic and protect against the challenge of wild type CoVs.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of vaccines are highly immunogenic and protect against the challenge of wild type CoVs?",
                    "answer": "vaccines based on protein S (especially receptor binding domain, RBD)"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of vaccines are based on protein S and RBD?",
                    "score": 0.8102,
                    "answers": "wild|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of CoV vaccines are highly immunogenic and protect against the challenge of wild type CoVs?",
                    "score": 0.7873,
                    "answers": "wild type|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of vaccines based on protein S?",
                    "score": 0.7524,
                    "answers": "wild type CoVs|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does RBD stand for?",
                    "score": 0.7001,
                    "answers": "on protein S ( especially receptor binding domain , RBD )|prep\tprotein|compound\tprotein S ( especially receptor binding domain , RBD )|pobj\tRBD|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the immunogenic effects of CoVs?",
                    "score": 0.6976,
                    "answers": "have|aux\t(|punct\tespecially|advmod\thighly|advmod\thighly immunogenic|acomp\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Vaccines that target other parts of the virus, such as nucleocapside, without S protein, have not shown protection against CoV infection and increased lung pathology.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that vaccines that target other parts of the CoV virus did not show protection against CoV infection and increased lung pathology?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What vaccines target other parts of the virus without S protein?",
                    "score": 0.8326,
                    "answers": "other|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of the CoV virus?",
                    "score": 0.7306,
                    "answers": "that target other parts of the virus , such as nucleocapside , without S protein|relcl\tagainst CoV infection|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of CoV?",
                    "score": 0.6988,
                    "answers": "CoV|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is nucleocapside?",
                    "score": 0.6858,
                    "answers": "such as nucleocapside|prep\tnucleocapside|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However, immunization with some protein S-based CoV vaccines has also shown signs of increased lung pathology following infection with the virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What has the immunization with the protein S-based CoV vaccine shown signs of?",
                    "answer": "increased lung pathology"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of immunization with protein S-based CoV vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7919,
                    "answers": "immunization with some protein S - based CoV vaccines|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of immunization with CoV vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.7716,
                    "answers": "protein S|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of immunization with some protein S-based CoV vaccines on lung pathology?",
                    "score": 0.7522,
                    "answers": "of increased lung pathology|prep\tincreased lung pathology|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between immunization with CoV vaccines and lung pathology?",
                    "score": 0.7255,
                    "answers": "lung|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is CoV?",
                    "score": 0.7079,
                    "answers": "CoV|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Therefore, in addition to the choice of antigen target, the efficacy of the vaccine and the risk of immunopathology may depend on other additional factors, such as the formulation of the adjuvant, the age of vaccination (..) and the route of immunization.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that the efficacy of the vaccine and the risk of immunopathology may depend on other factors?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What factors determine the efficacy of vaccines and immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7889,
                    "answers": "vaccination|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What other factors affect the efficacy of the vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7754,
                    "answers": "that Therefore , in addition to the choice of antigen target , the efficacy of the vaccine and the risk of immunopathology may depend on other additional factors , such as the formulation of the adjuvant , the age of vaccination ( .. ) and the route of immunization|ccomp\ton other additional factors , such as the formulation of the adjuvant , the age of vaccination ( .. ) and the route of immunization|prep\tother additional factors , such as the formulation of the adjuvant , the age of vaccination ( .. ) and the route of immunization|pobj\tof vaccination|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the ingredients of the adjuvant vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7169,
                    "answers": "antigen|compound\tof the vaccine|prep\tthe formulation of the adjuvant , the age of vaccination ( .. ) and the route of immunization|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the risk of immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6921,
                    "answers": "the risk of immunopathology|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the route of immunization?",
                    "score": 0.6688,
                    "answers": "the route of immunization|conj\tof immunization|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "“• BILD EINFÜGEN • NACHFOLGEND UNTERSTRICHEN MARKIERTE BILDBESCHREIBUNG • Antibody-mediated ADE and immunopathology • Left Panel: In ADE, the internalization of the immune complex is mediated by the involvement of activated Fc receptors on the cell surface.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that: • BILD EINFÜGEN • NACHFOLGEND UNTERSTRICHEN MARKIERTE BILDBESCHREIBUNG?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                },
                {
                    "question": "In ADE, the internalization of the immune complex is mediated by the involvement of what on the cell surface?",
                    "answer": "activated Fc receptors"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How is internalization of the immune complex mediated by the involvement of activated Fc receptors?",
                    "score": 0.8009,
                    "answers": "In ADE , the internalization of the immune complex is mediated by the involvement of activated Fc receptors on the cell surface|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are Antibody-mediated ADE and immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6623,
                    "answers": "that “ • BILD EINFÜGEN • NACHFOLGEND UNTERSTRICHEN MARKIERTE BILDBESCHREIBUNG • Antibody - mediated ADE and immunopathology •|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the functions of activated fc receptors?",
                    "score": 0.6604,
                    "answers": "activated Fc receptors|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the role of activated fc receptors in the internalization of immune complex?",
                    "score": 0.6521,
                    "answers": "of activated Fc receptors|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is BILD EINFÜGEN?",
                    "score": 0.6383,
                    "answers": "BILD|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Collegation of inhibitor receptors then leads to inhibition of antiviral reactions, leading to increased viral replication.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What leads to inhibition of antiviral reactions?",
                    "answer": "Collegation of inhibitor receptors"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of Collegation of inhibitor receptors on viral replication?",
                    "score": 0.7862,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Collegation of inhibitor receptors then leads to inhibition of antiviral reactions , leading to increased viral replication|ROOT\tantiviral|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the main causes of viral replication?",
                    "score": 0.7859,
                    "answers": "antiviral reactions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the effect of inhibition of inhibitor reactions on viral replication?",
                    "score": 0.7591,
                    "answers": "to inhibition of antiviral reactions|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is viral replication?",
                    "score": 0.7457,
                    "answers": "viral|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between acclation of inhibitor receptors and viral replication?",
                    "score": 0.735,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Right Panel: Antibodies may cause immunopathology by activating the complement pathway or antibody-dependent cell cytotoxicity (ADCC).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ADCC stand for?",
                    "answer": "activating the complement pathway or antibody-dependent cell cytotoxicity"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of antibodies on immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7181,
                    "answers": "that Right Panel : Antibodies may cause immunopathology by activating the complement pathway or antibody - dependent cell cytotoxicity ( ADCC )|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the possible side effects of antibodies?",
                    "score": 0.7006,
                    "answers": "Antibodies|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the Right Panel say about immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6803,
                    "answers": "by activating the complement pathway or antibody - dependent cell cytotoxicity ( ADCC|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies and cytotoxicity?",
                    "score": 0.6629,
                    "answers": "activating the complement pathway or antibody - dependent cell cytotoxicity ( ADCC|pcomp\tantibody - dependent|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ADCC stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6328,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t:|punct\tthe|det\t-|punct\tcell|compound\t(|punct\tADCC|appos\t)|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In both ways, excessive immunological activation leads to the release of cytokines and chemokines, resulting in an increase in disease pathology.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that excessive immunological activation leads to the release of cytokines and chemokines?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are chemokines?",
                    "score": 0.6994,
                    "answers": "chemokines|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the release of cytokines and chemokines?",
                    "score": 0.6843,
                    "answers": "to the release of cytokines and chemokines|prep\tthe release of cytokines and chemokines|pobj\tof cytokines and chemokines|prep\tcytokines and chemokines|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between cytokines and chemokines?",
                    "score": 0.6478,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tan increase in disease pathology|pobj\tdisease|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is disease pathology?",
                    "score": 0.6103,
                    "answers": "disease pathology|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The important risk-benefit analysis before decidingIn all probability, regardless of how effective (or ineffective) COVID-19 vaccines are, they will reach the public in a relatively short time.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that The important risk-benefit analysis before deciding?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How effective are COVID-19 vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8929,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\t25/11/2020|pobj\tregardless of how effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19 vaccines are|advmod\tof how effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19 vaccines are|prep\thow|advmod\thow effective ( or ineffective )|amod\tineffective )|conj\thow effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19|attr\thow effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19 vaccines are|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long does it take for COVID-19 vaccines to reach the public?",
                    "score": 0.8543,
                    "answers": "a relatively short time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long will COVID-19 vaccines last?",
                    "score": 0.8538,
                    "answers": "in a relatively short time|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the risks of COVID-19 vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8265,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that The important risk - benefit analysis before decidingIn all probability , regardless of how effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19 vaccines are , they will reach the public in a relatively short time|ROOT\timportant|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the chances that COVID-19 vaccines will reach the public?",
                    "score": 0.8149,
                    "answers": ", regardless of how effective ( or ineffective ) COVID-19 vaccines are , they will reach the public in a relatively short time|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Most predict that one or more vaccines will be ready sometime in 2021.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that most predict that one or more vaccines will be ready sometime in 2021?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many vaccines will be ready by 2021?",
                    "score": 0.7827,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat Most predict that one or more vaccines will be ready sometime in 2021|ccomp\tthat one or more vaccines will be ready sometime in 2021|ccomp\tready|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Ironically, the data we have now no longer support a mass vaccination mandate, considering that the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that Ironically, the data we no longer support a mass vaccination mandate?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60?",
                    "score": 0.7231,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Ironically , the data we have now no longer support a mass vaccination mandate , considering that the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza|ROOT\tthe data we have now|nsubj\tthat Ironically , the data we have now no longer support a mass vaccination mandate , considering that the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza|ccomp\tconsidering that the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza|advcl\tthe lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age|nsubj\tof COVID-19|prep\tCOVID-19|pobj\tthat the lethality of COVID-19 for people under 60 years of age is lower than that of influenza|ccomp\tlower than that of influenza|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the current vaccination rate for people under 60 years of age?",
                    "score": 0.6897,
                    "answers": "now|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the mass vaccination mandate?",
                    "score": 0.6739,
                    "answers": "mass|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If you're under 40, your risk of dying from COVID-19 is only 0.01%, which means you have a 99.99% chance of surviving the infection.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the chance of surviving COVID-19 if you're under 40?",
                    "answer": "99.99%"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the risk of dying from COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7292,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that If you 're under 40 , your risk of dying from COVID-19 is only 0.01 % , which means you have a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tIf|mark\tyou|nsubj\tIf you 're under 40|advcl\t40|pobj\t,|punct\tyour|poss\tyour risk of dying from COVID-19|nsubj\tof dying from COVID-19|prep\tdying from COVID-19|pcomp\tfrom COVID-19|prep\tCOVID-19|pobj\tthat If you 're under 40 , your risk of dying from COVID-19 is only 0.01 % , which means you have a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|ccomp\tonly|advmod\tonly 0.01|nummod\tonly 0.01 %|attr\t,|attr\twhich|nsubj\twhich means you have a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|advcl\tyou|nsubj\tyou have a 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|ccomp\ta|det\t99.99|nummod\t99.99 %|compound\ta 99.99 % chance of surviving the infection|dobj\tof surviving the infection|prep\tsurviving the infection|pcomp\tthe|det\tthe infection|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And you could improve it to 99.999% if you're metabolically flexible and rich in vitamin D. So, what are we protecting ourselves from with a vaccine against COVID-19?As already mentioned, vaccines are not even designed to prevent infection, but only to reduce the severity of symptoms.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said you could improve it to 99.999% if you're metabolically flexible and rich in vitamin D?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What percentage of COVID-19 could you improve if you're metabolically flexible and rich in vitamin D?",
                    "answer": "99.999%"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does a vaccine protect against?",
                    "answer": "COVID-19?"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the CDC say about vaccines against COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7969,
                    "answers": "So , are we protecting ourselves what from with a vaccine against COVID-19?As already mentioned , vaccines are not even designed to prevent infection , but only to reduce the severity of symptoms|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7217,
                    "answers": "rich in|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.7109,
                    "answers": ", vaccines are not even designed to prevent infection , but only to reduce the severity of symptoms|conj\tto prevent infection , but only to reduce the severity of symptoms|xcomp\tonly to reduce the severity of symptoms|conj\tthe severity of symptoms|dobj\tof symptoms|prep\tsymptoms|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6986,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tAnd|cc\tyou|nsubj\tcould|aux\tit|dobj\tif|mark\tyou|nsubj\tmetabolically|advmod\tand|cc\tin|prep\tSo|cc\t,|punct\twhat|pobj\tare|aux\twe|nsubj\tourselves|dobj\twhat from|prep\twith a vaccine against COVID-19?As|prep\ta|det\ta vaccine against COVID-19?As|pobj\tagainst COVID-19?As|prep\tCOVID-19?As|pobj\talready|advmod\talready mentioned|ccomp\t,|punct\tvaccines|nsubjpass\tare|auxpass\tnot|neg\teven|advmod\tto|aux\tinfection|dobj\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tonly|advmod\tto|aux\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.682,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tvitamin|compound\tvitamin D.|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the meantime, you might get sick more once you're exposed to the virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that you might get sick more once you're exposed to the virus?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How are you exposed to the virus?",
                    "score": 0.7591,
                    "answers": "once you 're exposed to the virus|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of the flu?",
                    "score": 0.6248,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This seems to be a great risk to a truly questionable benefit.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that this seemed to be a great risk to a truly questionable benefit?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does 2020news.de say about this questionable benefit?",
                    "score": 0.727,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This seems to be a great risk to a truly questionable benefit|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a questionable benefit to a truly questionable benefit?",
                    "score": 0.7029,
                    "answers": "to|aux\ta|det\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between questionable benefits and questionable benefits?",
                    "score": 0.6862,
                    "answers": "that This seems to be a great risk to a truly questionable benefit|ccomp\ttruly questionable|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the questionable benefit of the scam?",
                    "score": 0.6593,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "To get back to the starting point: Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials are not informed of this risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that Participants in the COVID-19 vaccine trials could make them more severe after they become infected with the virus?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials informed of the risk of the virus?",
                    "score": 0.8635,
                    "answers": "not|neg\tthat To get back to the starting point : Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials are not informed of this risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus|ccomp\tafter|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How severe is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.8077,
                    "answers": "them more severe|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the risks of the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7629,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that To get back to the starting point : Participants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials are not informed of this risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus|ROOT\tof this risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus|prep\tthis risk – that the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.7373,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tTo|aux\tthe|det\tstarting|compound\t:|punct\tParticipants in the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|nsubjpass\tin the ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|prep\tthe|det\tvaccine|compound\tthe ongoing COVID-19 vaccine trials|pobj\tare|auxpass\tthis|det\t–|punct\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe vaccine|nsubj\tcould|aux\tthat the vaccine could make them more severe COVID-19 after they become infected with the virus|acl\tthem|nsubj\tmore|advmod\tthem more severe COVID-19|dobj\tthey|nsubjpass\tbecome|auxpass\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.707,
                    "answers": "COVID-19|nmod\twith the virus|prep\tthe virus|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Fatal immunopathology Th2 is another potential risk.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is another potential risk?",
                    "answer": "Fatal immunopathology Th2"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the risks of fatal immunopathology Th2?",
                    "score": 0.82,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tanother|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the potential risk of fatal immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7916,
                    "answers": "another potential risk|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is fatal immunopathology Th2?",
                    "score": 0.7857,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that Fatal immunopathology Th2 is another potential risk|ROOT\tFatal immunopathology Th2|nsubj\tthat Fatal immunopathology Th2 is another potential risk|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between fatal immunopathology and Th2?",
                    "score": 0.7856,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is fatal immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7358,
                    "answers": "Fatal immunopathology|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Finally, think about what the information from the PNAS says about the risk of increase and dysfunction of the immune system induced by the vaccine, especially for the elderly, the same people who would need the protection that a vaccine should provide:\"Since the 1960s, tests of candidate vaccines for diseases such as dengue, syncitial respiratory virus (SRI) and severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) have shown a paradoxical phenomenon:Some animals or people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus developed a more serious disease than those who had not been vaccinated.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who developed a more serious disease than those who weren't vaccinated?",
                    "answer": "people who received the vaccine and later exposed themselves to the virus"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of the paradoxical phenomenon of candidate vaccines for diseases like dengue, syncitial respiratory virus (SRI) and severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS)?",
                    "score": 0.8007,
                    "answers": ", tests of candidate vaccines for diseases such as dengue , syncitial respiratory virus ( SRI ) and severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS ) have shown a paradoxical phenomenon|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does PNAS say about the risk of increase and dysfunction of the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.7928,
                    "answers": "Finally|advmod\twhat|dobj\timmune|amod\tespecially|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the flu vaccine and SARS?",
                    "score": 0.6921,
                    "answers": "SARS|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the risk of increased and dysfunction of immune system?",
                    "score": 0.6892,
                    "answers": "tests of candidate vaccines for diseases such as dengue , syncitial respiratory virus ( SRI ) and severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS )|nsubj\tof candidate vaccines for diseases such as dengue , syncitial respiratory virus ( SRI ) and severe acute respiratory syndrome ( SARS )|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does SRI stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6619,
                    "answers": "respiratory|amod\tSRI|appos\trespiratory|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The immune system supported by the vaccine seemed to trigger an incorrect response to natural infection in certain cases (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that the immune system supported by the vaccine seemed to trigger an incorrect response to natural infection in certain cases?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the immune system do to trigger a natural infection?",
                    "score": 0.7253,
                    "answers": "to trigger an incorrect response to natural infection in certain cases|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the immune system that trigger an incorrect response to natural infection in certain cases?",
                    "score": 0.648,
                    "answers": "the|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This reflammation of the immune system, known as immune enhancement, can manifest itself in several ways, including antibody-dependent enhancement (ADE), a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection, or cell-based enhancement, a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "answer": "antibody-dependent enhancement"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of antibodies are used for immune enhancement?",
                    "score": 0.7884,
                    "answers": "antibodies|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is allergic inflammation?",
                    "score": 0.6839,
                    "answers": "that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|relcl\tallergic|amod\tallergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between antibodies and immune enhancement?",
                    "score": 0.6715,
                    "answers": "antibody|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is immune enhancement?",
                    "score": 0.6677,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement , can manifest itself in several ways , including antibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|ROOT\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tThis|det\tThis reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement ,|nsubj\tof the immune system|prep\tthe|det\timmune|amod\tthe immune system|pobj\t,|punct\tknown as immune enhancement|acl\tas immune enhancement|prep\timmune|amod\timmune enhancement|pobj\t,|punct\tcan|aux\tthat This reflammation of the immune system , known as immune enhancement , can manifest itself in several ways , including antibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|ccomp\titself|dobj\tin several ways , including antibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|prep\tseveral|amod\tseveral ways , including antibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|pobj\t,|punct\tincluding antibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|prep\t-|punct\tantibody - dependent|amod\tantibody - dependent enhancement ( ADE ) , a process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection , or cell - based enhancement , a category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|pobj\t(|punct\t)|punct\t,|punct\ta|det\ta process in which a virus uses antibodies to support infection|appos\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\ta|det\ta virus|nsubj\tin which a virus uses antibodies to support infection|relcl\tto|aux\tto support infection|xcomp\tinfection|dobj\t,|punct\tor|cc\t-|punct\t,|punct\ta|det\ta category that includes allergic inflammation caused by Th2 immunopathology|appos\tthat|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ADE stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6608,
                    "answers": "ADE|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In some cases, improvement processes can overlap (..).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said on 25/11/2020 that improvement processes can overlap?",
                    "answer": "2020news.de"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can improvement processes overlap?",
                    "score": 0.8322,
                    "answers": "can|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between improvement processes and improvement processes?",
                    "score": 0.6796,
                    "answers": "on 25/11/2020|prep\tIn some cases|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Some researchers argue that although ADE has received the greatest attention so far, according to what is known about the epidemiology of the virus and its behavior in the human body, it is less likely to occur than a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What do some researchers believe about ADE?",
                    "answer": "it is less likely to occur than a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How is deregulated response to COVID-19 determined?",
                    "score": 0.7318,
                    "answers": "through other means of immunological improvement|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the rate of deregulated response to COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6855,
                    "answers": "that Some researchers argue that although ADE has received the greatest attention so far , according to what is known about the epidemiology of the virus and its behavior in the human body , it is less likely to occur than a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement|ccomp\tthat although ADE has received the greatest attention so far , according to what is known about the epidemiology of the virus and its behavior in the human body , it is less likely to occur than a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement|ccomp\tless|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the methods that can be used to prevent the spread of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6777,
                    "answers": "of immunological improvement|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6703,
                    "answers": "a deregulated response to COVID-19 through other means of immunological improvement|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID-19?",
                    "score": 0.6577,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tSome|det\tthat|mark\tADE|nsubj\tthe|det\tgreatest|amod\twhat|nsubjpass\tthe|det\tof the virus|prep\tthe|det\tthe virus|pobj\tits|poss\tits behavior in the human body|conj\tin the human body|prep\tthe|det\thuman|amod\tthe human body|pobj\tto|aux\ta|det\tto COVID-19|prep\tCOVID-19|pobj\timmunological|amod\timmunological improvement|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "‘ADE may occur, but the biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology', says Ralph Baric, an epidemiologist and coronavirus expert (..) at North Carolina University in Chapel Hill.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is Ralph Baric from?",
                    "answer": "North Carolina University"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Ralph Baric say about Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.7327,
                    "answers": "may|aux\tNorth|compound\tChapel|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the biggest problem with Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6845,
                    "answers": "2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that ‘ ADE may occur , but the biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology|ccomp\ton 25/11/2020|prep\tthat|mark\tthat ‘ ADE may occur , but the biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology|ccomp\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tthe|det\tbiggest|amod\tthe biggest problem|nsubj\tthe biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology|conj\tprobably|advmod\t'|punct\t,|punct\t2020news.de said on 25/11/2020 that ‘ ADE may occur , but the biggest problem is probably Th2 immunopathology ' , says Ralph Baric , an epidemiologist and coronavirus expert ( .. ) at North Carolina University in Chapel Hill|ROOT\tRalph|compound\tRalph Baric , an epidemiologist and coronavirus expert ( .. ) at North Carolina University in Chapel Hill|nsubj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tcoronavirus|compound\t(|punct\t..|punct\tin Chapel Hill|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6748,
                    "answers": "Th2|compound\tTh2 immunopathology|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Ralph Baric's work on Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6695,
                    "answers": "North Carolina|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6494,
                    "answers": "‘|punct\tan|det\tcoronavirus expert|conj\t)|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In previous studies on SARS, it was discovered that older mice were at a particularly high risk of developing a life-threatening Th2 immunopathology, (..) in which a defective T-cell response triggers allergic inflammation and malfunctioning antibodies that form immune complexes activate the complement system and can damage the respiratory tract.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "answer": "a defective T-cell response triggers allergic inflammation"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are older mice at a particularly high risk of developing a life-threatening Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.8821,
                    "answers": "older|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does defective T-cell response do to the respiratory tract?",
                    "score": 0.6979,
                    "answers": "can damage the respiratory tract|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the risks of Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6716,
                    "answers": "life - threatening|amod\tthe respiratory tract|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the role of defective T-cell response in developing Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6635,
                    "answers": "that form immune complexes|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Th2 immunopathology?",
                    "score": 0.6522,
                    "answers": "developing a life - threatening Th2 immunopathology , ( .. ) in which a defective T - cell response triggers allergic inflammation and malfunctioning antibodies that form immune complexes activate the complement system and can damage the respiratory tract|pcomp\tTh2|compound\ta life - threatening Th2 immunopathology , ( .. ) in which a defective T - cell response triggers allergic inflammation and malfunctioning antibodies that form immune complexes activate the complement system and can damage the respiratory tract|dobj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}